al al
al al
[Music]
[Música]
ok here here we
ok here here we
Go for the family here perform it for
Go for the family here perform it for
you if you know the words you can join
you if you know the words you can join
In To put your hands Together if you W
In To put your hands Together if you W
Clap as we take you through this monkey
Clap as we take you through this monkey
[Music]
[Música]
rapke
rapke
Kong Donkey
Kong Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong He's the leader of the
Kong Donkey Kong He's the leader of the
bunch you know him well He's Finally
bunch you know him well He's Finally
back to Kick some ta his Coconut gum and
back to Kick some ta his Coconut gum and
sps If he shoots G
sps If he shoots
hur He's bger faster and stronger to
G hur He's bger faster and stronger to
he First member of the d
he First member of the d
Crew  Donkey
Crew Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
iskey
iskey
[Music]
[Música]
Donkey
Donkey
Donkey si
Donkey si
She quick and When She needs to be She
She quick and When She needs to be She
can FL through the air and Climb up tre
can FL through the air and Climb up tre
if you choose her You're not choosing
if you choose her You're not choose
wrong with a skip and a H She's One cool
wrong with a skip and a H She's One cool
car Donkey
car Donkey
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Kong Donkey Kong is here
d Donkey
d Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is H he has no Style he
Kong Donkey Kong is H he has no Style he
has no
has no
[Music]
[Música]
Grace has a funny Face he can hand
Grace has a funny Face he can
when  he needs to and stretch his
hand when he needs to and stretch his
Arms out  Just for you inflate himself
Arms out Just for you inflate himself
just like a balloon this Crazy Just digs
just like a balloon this Crazy Just digs
hisun Donkey
hisun Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Kong Donkey Kong is here
dk Donkey Kong
dk Donkey Kong
dk Donkey Kong is
dk Donkey Kong is
[Music]
[Música]
donke
donke
Kong donke Kong He's Back Again and
Kong donke Kong He's Back Again and
about time to and this Time He's in the
about time to and this Time He's in the
mo he can fly real with his Jet on with
mo he can fly real with his Jet on with
his pistols out He's One tough c he'll
his pistols out He's One tough c he'll
Make You Smile when he Plays butlin
Make You Smile when he Plays butlin
beware he after you
beware he after you
Donkey
Donkey
[Music]
[Música]
Kong Donkey  Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
here Donkey
here Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is here Finally He's here
Kong Donkey Kong is here Finally He's
for you It's The Last member of the
here for you It's The Last member of the
dk Crew this K so strong it isn't funny
dk Crew this K so strong it isn't funny
make a klin Cry out for mmy pick up a b
make a klin Cry out for mmy pick up a b
with rel e makes crushing Rocks seem
with rel e makes crushing Rocks seem
such a bree he May move Slow can't jump
such a bree he May move Slow can't jump
High but this com One Hell Of A Come on
High but this com One Hell Of A Come on
cranky take it to the fridge
cranky take it to the fridge
[Music]
[Música]
walut peut
walut peut
pelles Mel oranges and cocut shell  Oh
pelles Mel oranges and cocut shell Oh
yeah walnuts peut pine
yeah walnuts peut pine
smell Mel  oranges and coconut shell oh
smell Mel oranges and Coconut shell oh
yeah walnuts peut pineapple
yeah walnuts peut pineapple
smells melons oranges and coconut shell oh [
smells melons oranges and Coconut shell
Music]
[Música]
m
m
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Sparkle
Sparkle
[Music]
[Música]
Oh
Oh
H
H
[Music] [Music
[Música]
[Applause] [Music]
[Aplausos]
come on [
venga
Music]
[Música]
he he he he he Hey he he Hey hey
he he he
[Music] head
[Música]
Hey
heod Hey
he felo
he felo
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
felo Oregon
felo Oregon
tur
tur
turle you
turle you
[Music]
[Música]
Mario Oh [
Mario Oh
Mario
Mario
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
and
y
Ho
Ho
[Music] [
[Música]
Applause]
[Aplausos]
Well very well What's up How
Pues muy bien Qué pasa Cómo
are you What's up How
estáis Qué pasa Qué
angry I am about poor Fran Well you
Rabiosa me tiene lo del pobre Fran Pues
see the truth is that he told me  A
ya ves la verdad es que a mí me lo contó
few days ago and little by little she's been
Hace unos días y poco a poco me ha ido
telling me what she's about and well now
diciendo de lo que va y bueno ahora
when the time comes we'll go in and we'll
cuando llegue el momento entraremos y lo
talk about it but wow Hi grandpa
y lo comentaremos pero tela Hola abuelo
in Mexico we're mourning
en México estamos de luto se murió
Paquita from the dp neighborhood died so here's a
Paquita la del barrio dp así que ahí un
little tribute filthy rat
pequeño tributo rata inmunda animal
crawling animal Scum Of life adecio poorly
rastrero Escoria De la vida adecio mal
done subhuman damn vermin
hecho infrahumano [__] sabandija Rata
Two-legged rat I'm talking to you What a shame
de dos patas te estoy hablando Qué pena
What a shame how life goes by eh Well
Qué pena cómo va pasando la vida eh Pues
yes we send all the love in the
sí le le mandamos todo el cariño del
world to the family eh or at least
mundo a la familia eh o por lo menos
good vibes no because Surely
buenas vibras no porque Seguro seguro
there's no one who's going to see us from
que no hay nadie que nos va a ver de la
her family obviously but but
familia de ella evidentemente pero pero
good vibes good good vibes an anthem
buenas vibras buenas buenas vibras un
anthem a wonderful anthem
himno un himno un himno maravilloso nos
left us Eh well family well today we have
dejó Eh bueno familia pues hoy tenemos
some little thing to screw up 1 uh 1:10
alguna cosilla que [__] la 1 eh la 1:10
starting here live my goodness you
empezando aquí en directo madre mía me
have me staying up all night eh I'm going to have to
tenéis trasnochando eh voy a tener que
Cancel something There's one of the there's one of
Cancelar algo Hay uno de los hay uno de
the three channels there's one of the three
los tres canales hay una de las tres
things that I do that I'm going to Have to leave
cosas que hago que voy Tiene que dejar
at some
en algún
point I don't know which  and how but I was
momento no sé cuál y cómo pero lo esty
talking about it last night with luares there is one of
hablando anoche con luares hay una de
the things that I'm going to have to leave I do
las cosas que que voy a tener que dejar
n't know
no sé
when I don't know if it will be soon I don't know if it will be
cuándo no sé si será pronto no sé si
in the distant future but of course we are on
será en un futuro lejano pero claro
the main channel we are at the salsería and we are teles sals So in reality it would be worth it with any of the three jobs in reality it would be worth it with any of the three jobs we are doing all three I mean the reality would be of any streamer well the reality of any streamer is the channel whatever it is or
es el canal que sea o sea o bien lo que
what I do on the main channel or what I do at
yo hago en el canal principal o bien lo
the salsería or what I
que hago en la salsería o bien lo que
do at telesalseo
hago en telesalseo
but not all three eh all three are very
pero no los tres eh los tres es muy
beastly it is very beastly Let's see I don't know I
bestia es muy bestia A ver no sé me
imagine that I imagine that the movement
imagino que me imagino que la movida
will surely be e
será seguramente
I think that the youtuber of youtubers
e Yo creo que el youtuber de youtubers
the gossip of the youtubers
los salseos de los youtubers
and not leaving it completely okay Not leaving it
e no dejarlo del todo vale No dejarlo
completely but maybe eh I think that
del todo pero a lo mejor eh Yo creo que
because of age it will surely be what at
por edad seguramente será lo que en
some point not leaving it completely but we will
algún momento no dejarlo del todo sino
only come to comment
que solamente vendremos a comentar
when the strong topics
cuando sean los temas fuertes temas
relevant topics you know not topic of Oh look a
relevantes sabes no tema de Ay mira un
hater said burn them and something they're
hater ha dicho quemarlos y y algo son
twin brothers I mean this is tremendous
hermanos gemelos o sea esto es tremendo
eh the issue of
eh el tema de los
haters the issue of haters is tremendous
haters el tema de los haters es tremendo
eh Oy let's see here a few of the
eh Oy vamos a ver aquí unas cuantas de
things that haters have with uncle
movidas que tienen los haters con el tío
sh and gibel and so on if I've left something
sh y gibel y demás no si me dejo algo
behind let me know We also have
por atrás hacérmelo saber También
a goal today that's going to
tenemos un objetivo hoy que os va a
motivate you eh it's going to motivate you not to donate
motivar eh os va a motivar a que no doné
a turkey today the goal of Super chat is
un pavo hoy el objetivo de Super chat es
a button against Javi El
un botón contra Javi El
pelucas javiel pelucas This is a guy
pelucas javiel pelucas Este es un chico
Uh I got into his Twitter account
Eh me he metido en su cuenta de Twitter
or rather eh more than anything to put you
o sea eh más que nada para para poneros
in context okay because this is
un poco en contexto vale porque este es
a guy who made the following video
un chico que ha hecho el siguiente vídeo
and the haters are applauding him because he
y los haters lo están aplaudiendo porque
made the following video and that Argos
ha hecho el siguiente vídeo y que Argos
and Marlos are
y marlos son
brothers I don't know if he was talking about
hermanos no sé si estaba hablando de
Argos and Marlos or their parents okay but he
Argos y marlos o de sus padres vale pero
said it okay I mean This video is being
lo ha dicho vale o sea Este vídeo lo
shared well well look at all
están compartiendo pues pues miad toda
these people okay This video is being
esta gente vale Este vídeo lo están
shared like the brutal video that this one
compartiendo como el vídeo brutal que ha
made  kid okay I mean they don't care what it is
hecho este chaval vale o sea les vale lo
eh Wait a
que sea eh Espérate un
minute Of course I went to see
momento Pues claro yo me he metido a ver
who he is or what he was
quién es o qué
doing I went to see that that that
hacía me he metido a ver que que que de
where this man came from Okay and it turns
dónde había salido este hombre Vale y
out that by going into his
resulta ser que metiéndome en su
account the twists towards me are How old is he
cuenta los twist hacia a mí son Qué edad
grandpa you're [ __ ] These are in
abuelo eres subnormal Estos son en
response to me okay love yourself a
respuesta a mí vale quiérete un
little here me asking Editors and he says you
poco aquí yo pidiendo Editores y dice
prefer them Latinos too right
los prefieres latinos también verdad
like your master I say fact this eh fact is
como tu amo Digo facto esto eh facto es
eh MMM
eh MMM
that Ricky was right and I wasn't about the
que Ricky tenía la razón y yo no en el
strikes okay because when he
tema de los strike vale porque cuando él
puts them in it's okay because to him I mean
los mete está bien porque a él o sea
when they call a strike on him it's not
cuando a él le ponen strike no están
right because Ricky has
bien porque a Ricky no le han tirado
never had a video shot and they called me you
nunca un vídeo y a mí me la han tirado
see the difference
ves la diferencia
[Music]
[Música]
and the tone is this okay the
e la tónica es esta vale
Javi Oliveira fans are
lo de los fan de Javi oliveira es
scary he's
acojonante está
pissed off good
picado buen
challenge Loilo no no no don't support that challenge it
reto loilo no no no no apoyéis ese reto
's against Javil Pelucas
que es contra javil pelucas
eh from here I publicly apologize to
eh desde aquí pido perdón públicamente a
csita and to Ja Oliveira  slander and
csita y a ja oliveira calumnias y
out of place comments that I
comentarios fuera de lugar de los cuales
regret Oh I mean woof woof I mean
me arrepiento Ah o sea guau guau o sea
the guy Mira woof woof said the
el tío Mira guau guau dijo el
little dog I mean the guy Mira was laughing at
perrito O sea el tipo Mira se reía de lo
the conversations of Miare that
de las conversaciones de miare las que
Win michu published but he was laughing at her
publicó Win michu pero se reía de ella
not at the conversations I mean the guy
no de de las conversaciones o sea el tío
was like on my behalf he was trying to
estaba como de parte mía intentaba como
get closer to me so I would pay attention to him then
acercarse que le diera bola luego
for a while he insulted me with the
durante una época me insultaba con lo de
little dog thing I don't know what I don't know how much and
perrito No sé qué no sé cuánto y luego
then finally he apologized as
pues finalmente me me pidió perdón como
if I had found out what the
si yo me Hubiera enterado de lo que
[ __ ] he had said to me God knows what it
[__] me hubiera dicho vete tú a saber
was and then again no way I don't
lo que sería y ya luego otra vez no
like I didn't pay attention to him well he
e como no le como no le hice
acquired the role of
caso pues adquirió el papel otra vez de
little dog again and those things no
perrito y esas cosas no a
way but
ver pero
well the level is this and that Argos and
bueno el nivel es este y que Argos y
Marlos are brothers Why do I say this And
marlos son hermanos Por qué digo esto Y
why am I supporting this fact because I have been
por qué estoy apoyando este hecho porque
able to get more than one proof I have
he podido conseguir más que una prueba
gotten several although this and that
he conseguido varias aunque esto y que
Argos and Marlos are brothers he has
Argos y marlos son hermanos ha
gotten a lot of proof okay I will
conseguido muchas pruebas vale lo
repeat it again there I say that they are
repetiré otra vez ahí digo que son
brothers belonging to the same
hermanos pertenecientes a la misma
litter if you don't have the neurons to
camada si no te dan las neuronas para
think  without making you gossips it's not
pensar sin hacértelas chismosas no es
my fault your mom is very hot
mía tu mamá está muy buena
Javi in ​​the Sur video the serl gives me the
Javi en el vídeo de Sur la serl me da la
role of my life in the first two
pape de mi vida en los primeros dos
minutes Sur is calculating the amount
minutos Sur está calculando la cantidad
of tweets that El pelucas dedicated to you
de tweets que El pelucas te dedicó a ti
and aas Haha In case you want to see it eh
y aas Jaja Por si lo quieres ver eh
[Music]
[Música]
it's that it's 44 minutes Ah the first 2
es que son 44 minutos Ah los primeros 2
minutes okay I'm putting it here for when
minutos vale Lo pongo aquí para cuando
we get to javel peluca is that they are
lleguemos a javel peluca es que son
all haters today they are all haters This
todos hater hoy son todos hater Este
first excerpt are all haters no I mean
primer extracto son todos hater no O sea
here we see the shur who is fighting
aquí vemos al shur que se está peleando
with laser len or laser len I
con laser len o sea laser len yo lo de
really don't understand what this man is doing I mean I do
este hombre no lo entiendo de verdad o
n't know if it's because I already said it
sea es que no sé si es porque ya lo dije
yesterday no also no I mean the things he's
ayer no también no o sea las cosas que
doing today I saw him calling
está haciendo hoy lo he visto llamando
Dallas an abuser again I mean but an abuser
otra vez a Dallas maltratador o sea pero
abuser psychologist or
maltratador maltratador psicólogo óg
animal abuser also groomer
maltratador de animales también groomer
and all these things I don't understand it I mean I'm
y todas estas cosas no lo entiendo o sea
really trying to understand eh I mean
de verdad lo intento entender eh o sea
I want to think [ __ ] he's
quiero pensar [__] es que se está
making a fortune win  200 bucks because he says he
forrando gana 200 pavos porque él dice
does it for money No in fact we have
que lo hace por dinero No de hecho hemos
filed several lawsuits
presentado en las demandas varios clies
in which he claims he does it for
en las que él afirma que lo hace por
money but of course I understand that when he
dinero pero claro entiendo que cuando él
says he does it for money it is because His
dice que lo hace por dinero es porque Su
content is literally
contenido es literalmente
This is worth it he tries to make a video on
Esto vale él intenta hacer un vídeo de
any other topic 500 views okay and he
cualquier otro tema 500 visitas vale y
starts defaming me and dala and it's
se pone a difamar me a mí a dala y son
5000, well we're talking about 4 euros I don't know
5000 sea estamos hablando de 4 eur no sé
4 euros 3 euros something like that no [ __ ] you
4 eur 3 eur alguna cosa así no [__]
look at you eh 700
fíjate tú eh 700
views 1000 with the Elon Mask thing anyway
visitas 1000 con lo de elon Mask en fin
Of course I understand that when he says he
Claro entiendo que cuando él dice que lo
does it for money it's that I don't know it's like
hace por dinero es eso no sé es como
someone who got
alguien
frustrated because I didn't
e que se ha frustrado porque no le
want to be a youtuber for no reason he tried to be
quería ser youtuber por huevo él intentó
my editor he asked me to be my
ser mi editor me pidió ser mi
editor he tried to be my fan then he went
Editor intentó ser fan mío luego se fue
to write to Dallas privately
a escribirle a Dallas por privado por
please I have defended you Look at my video I don't
favor te he defendido Mira mi vídeo no
know what
sé qué
no And of course he got into this
no Y como no pues se ha metido en este
what this kid that
lo que acaba de hacer el chaval este que
we saw just did or rather no but he's already
hemos visto o sea sin más No pero ya se
gone  you don't know that when level
le ha ido no sabes que ya cuando nivel
and level you have demands
e nivel tienes demandas
complaints that you have them complicated, I
denuncias que las tienes complicadas o
mean, I'm not going to guess the future
sea yo no voy a adivinar el futuro
because I'm not the best at making
porque no soy el mejor haciendo
predictions about judicial matters
predicciones de los temas judiciales
but man Maria is gorgeous a kiss you
pero hombre María guapísima un beso
know but
sabes pero
H I don't know it's not that it doesn't occur to me to
H No sé no es que a mí no se me ocurre a
a person who has
una persona que me tenga
sued me to call you a disgusting [ __ ] I mean
demandado decirle [__] asquerosa O sea
imagine that someone I mean you can't
imagínate que alguien o sea tú no puedes
say everything you think no many
decir todo lo que piensas no muchas
times no but imagine any
veces no pero imagínate cualquier
person who sues you And you You raise the
persona que te demande Y tú Tú subas el
level disgusting [ __ ] son of a [ __ ] [ __ ]
nivel [__] asquerosa hijo de [__] cabrón
you understand I mean it doesn't make sense it doesn't
me entiendes O sea no tiene sentido no
cross my mind I wish it fits on
se me pasa por la cabeza Ojalá cabe en
the street but I don't know I mean I don't
la calle pero que no lo sé o sea yo no
I don't wish him anything bad or Well I don't care what I
yo ni le deseo nada malo ni Bueno a mí
consider
me da igual yo lo que lo que considero
is that he has violated a lot of
es que ha vulnerado un montón de de
things and that he has to pay just like that I
cosas y que tiene que pagar sea sin más
mean but I see it
O sea pero es que lo veo
logically it's less than Dallas I mean
logiques es menos que Dallas O sea que
Dallas is worse than yeah yeah let's go to it let's
Dallas es peor que sí sí vamos a ello
see but not this one but if
vamos a verlo pero que este no pero si
I have said it I mean yeah yeah suddenly I
yo lo he dicho O sea si si de repente yo
I make a video or I make a
le hago un vídeo o yo hago un una
criticism of José Bretón they defend
crítica a José bretón ellos defienden a
José Bretón but if I have said that
José bretón pero si eso lo he dicho ya
many times and they were
un montón de veces y se indignaron
very outraged when I said it like no it is not
muchísimo cuando lo di como no no es
literal it is literal eh they are talking
literal es literal eh se están hablando
to raed I mean but both he and
con raed o sea pero tanto él como la
my mother talk to raed uncle raed
mamá de mi se hablan con raed tío raed
literally was part of pambi
literalmente era parte de pambi no
weren't you very outraged with pambi
estabais muy indignados con pambi
pending that I have already made RAE
pendiente que ya le he hecho RAE
literally the audios of RAE
literalmente los audios de de RAE
yelling at his girlfriend on the phone
gritándole a la novia por teléfono
because she did not answer her or come on r is a
porque no la atendía o vamos r es una
person who no no it should not be treated
persona que que no no se debería tratar
as a side it is not sevill betti I mean r
de un bando no es sevill betti o sea r
is a person who is objectively
es una persona que es objetivamente
delinquent and violent I mean how are you going to
delincuente y violenta o sea cómo te vas
talk to that person if he is super
a hablar con esa persona si está super
involved against abusers it makes no
involucrado contra los maltratadores no
sense it makes no sense at all
tiene sentido no tiene sentido ninguno
well let's see what is happening to the south
bueno a ver qué es lo que le pasa al sur
that they are messing with him for what
que se están metiendo con él por qué
context I was watching exactly
contexto yo estuve viendo exactamente
What is the amount of Twitch and what is
Cuál es la cantidad de Twitch y cuál es
the amount of Well yes of Twitch that
la cantidad de Bueno sí de Twitch que
javel peluca puts ah this is [ __ ]
pone javel peluca ah que esto es [__]
This is the cin  what have you told me
Este es el cin que me habéis dicho
wait I'm going to leave it here because
espérate lo voy a dejar por aquí porque
this is around here when we enter abil
esto es por aquí cuando entramos a abil
peluca
peluca
today here he messes with uncle shur I don't know if
hoy aquí se mete con tío shur No sé si
you remember because there was a tweet from
os acordáis porque hubo un tweet de un
one of the haters that said that dala
de uno de los haters que ponía que dala
[ __ ] his
se follaba a su
sister okay And then uncle shur put
hermana vale Y entonces el tío shur puso
the screenshot as if to say damn what the [ __ ] is this
la captura como diciendo [__] qué [__]
awful What the [ __ ] is this awful I
barbaridad Qué [__]
also tell you
barbaridad también te digo
not specifically uncle shur okay But there are
no en concreto el tío shur vale Pero hay
some of them from the chat
algunos de ellos de los de la tertulia
that have fed this type of
que han alimentado este tipo de
community and to the one who doesn't give
comunidad y a la que a la que no le a la
them the food they get a
que no les da el alimento se salen un
little out of that food they go against them I
poco de ese alimento se van contra ellos
understand I mean they are not healthy people a
me enti O sea no son gente sana una
person who [ __ ] is that you are not
persona que coge es que no estás
criticizing aas for his song damn what the
criticando aas por su canción [__] qué
[ __ ] is the song is no no you're
[__] [__] la canción es no no estás
saying already on the way well Dalas
diciendo ya de camino pues Dalas se
[ __ ] his sister you understand me And
[__] la hermana me entiendes Y
surely in one of the comments
seguramente en alguno de los comentarios
on the video that one of
del del vídeo que hiciera alguno de
them will say Javi dog Haha Why does
ellos pondrá Javi perro Jaja Para qué
Dalas sing a song If Javi dog
Dalas canta una canción Si Javi perro
has a
tiene
flea I  you understand, I mean, these are things that
pulga me entiendes o sea son cosas que
they are now realizing, for
ahora ellos se están dando cuenta no por
example, now we're going to see what Gibel does, he is not
ejemplo ahora vamos a ver lo de gibel no
shocked by something that says jail
que se impacta de una cosa que diga jail
peluca and I have told him but then it
peluca y le he dicho yo pero entonces si
is the least that he dispatches well Well it
es lo mínimo que despacha bueno Pues
turns out that Uncle Shur takes out the
resulta ser que el tío shur saca la
capture and says
captura y dice
that what an outrage, not logical what
que qué barbaridad no lo lógico lo que
anyone would say no Well then Lerl
diríamos cualquiera no Bueno pues lerl
is criticizing Uncle Shur for having
está criticando al tío shur por haber
exposed that capture that is
expuesto esa captura que eso es
whitewashing
blanquear a
Dallas Gibel has already done quite a bit of cleaning up
Dallas gibel ya hizo bastante limpieza
in his chat Oh yeah well I'm glad man
en su chat Ah sí pues yo me alegro tío
because I really don't dislike him I mean
porque en realidad no me cae mal o sea
really it's that I don't dislike Gibel I mean I
realmente es que no me cae mal gibel o
even have grace and
sea creo que incluso tiene gracia y
charisma and things no what happens is that he
carisma y cosas no lo que pasa es que se
goes too far he
le va muchas veces no
goes too far Richel Critic
se le va muchas veces richel crítico
also trying to get on the vine I don't
intentando también subirse a la Parra No
think Laser Len has more visits than
creo que laser len tiene más visitas que
the stutterer And he is more well known and relevant
el tartaja Y es más conocido y relevante
than Tommy well Richel
que Tommy bueno richel
Critic and Here the thing begins
crítico y Aquí empieza la vaina
no Here the thing begins with Cris
no Aquí empieza la vaina de lo de Cris
Chan I mean I have been looking at the case a little bit
Chan o sea He estado mirando un poco el
because we have never
caso por encima porque nunca hemos
talked about  Cris, I mean, I had no
hablado de lo de Cris o sea no tenía ni
[ __ ] idea, I don't know if that case happened
[__] idea yo ese caso no sé si ha sido
at some point when he caught us with someone
en algún momento que nos ha pillado con
else, no, no, I haven't seen it, but
otro lo que no no no lo he visto pero
apparently it's a guy who's
por lo visto es un tío que es que ha
been in jail. Well, if they talk
cumplido cárcel Bueno pero si se hablan
to Tania and they support
con la Tania y apoyan a la
Tania, yes, they support Tania, what they
Tania si apoyan a la Tania que lo que le
're telling Tania is, Hey Tania, what are
están sacando a la Tania es Oye Tania
you defending your
que es que tú estás defendiendo a tu
husband, your husband has been in
marido que tu marido ha estado en la
jail for sleeping with
cárcel por estar acostándose 4 años con
a 10-
una niña de 10
year-old girl for 4 years, you know, it's like. Well, then they talk
años sabes es como Bueno pues se hablan
to Tania. And Tania, all my support and
con la Tania Y Tania todo mi apoyo y
Tania, a kiss, I mean, it doesn't make any
Tania un beso o sea es que no tiene
sense. Chis Chan, it's all crazy. Well, I
sentido chis Chan es todo una locura
have no idea about that case, right?
pues no tengo ni idea de ese caso no
But anyway,
Pero
here the tosur says exposing a
bueno aquí el tosur dice exponer a un
guy who says that he F's his sister is
tío que dice que d se F a su hermana es
whitewashing him, the level is scary. Oh,
blanquearlo el nivel es acojonante Ay
there's one
hay una
thing, well, Ah, but I think it was in the
cosa bueno Ah pero creo que fue en el
debate, no, there's something that he said
debate no que hay una cosa que le dijo
about the lawsuits, no, the guy shuro, it's that I've
sobre las demandas no el tío shuro es
seen the clip but I don't know,
que he visto el clip pero no sé
a kiss Senda, but how many  you have complaints I
un beso Senda pero cuántas denuncias
know of course I am I am a coward good
sabes claro yo so yo soy un [__] bueno
and a defendant dude that's it there you have to
y un demandado tío ya está hay hay que
differentiate between knowing Being brave and
diferenciar entre saber Ser valiente y
stupid How many drinks does the ler have
estúpido Cuántas copas tiene el ler ha
donated it was something about the lawsuits but he has
donado era algo sobre las demandas pero
n't done it
no me
because he doesn't want to receive lawsuits
ha porque no quiere recibir demandas
Well okay I think he's
Bueno está bien
brave
me parece valiente
laser what does Javi have to do with it here and up the
láser qu tiene que ver Javi aquí and por
ass every day toupee being an [ __ ] every day
culo toos los días peluquín dando por
not only because I didn't report
días no solamente porque noer denunci
also have this guy being an [ __ ] every
adem ten ch este peln dando por culo to
day toupee being an [ __ ] every
los días peluquín dando por culo todos
day this is daily the
días esto es a diario el
shawl and he thinks that nothing's going to happen
chal y cree que no va pasar nada
pressure but the worst thing is that
presiones pero es que lo peor es que
this guy
este tipo
was like a super defender super
e estaba como super defensor super
indignant that I the one that they
indignado de que yo la de que a mí me
condemned me because I called him a crazy old woman or a
condenaran porque le dije vieja loca o
broom hair I don't know who he is like a guy who
pelo escoba no sé quién es como tío que
spends all [ __ ] day
te pegas todo el [__] día
insulting all day and that I'm annoying
insultando todo el día y que yo le estoy
him boy who
dando por culo a él per chico que
appears in every
apareces en cada
tweet appears in every tweet of mine appears
tweet aparece en cada tweet mío aparece
insulting appears today appeared in one of my
insultando aparece hoy apareció en un
tweets saying calling me a failure
twit mío diciendo llamándome fracasado
bad the poor people of the  chat now they
mal los pobres de la tertulia ahora
are seeing what you have suffered
están viendo lo que vos has sufrido
grandfather who are you these people evil
abuelo quies vos esta gente malita
propaganda 2019 does not work They would not
propaganda 2019 no cuela Ya ellos no
put up with four or five
aguantarían que salgan cuatro o cinco
accounts being revealed, I would eh I
cuentas yo sí eh A mí me me la pela por
completely do not care if they come out, they even seem
completo que salgan me parecen incluso
necessary to me part of my job no but they would not put up with it they would not put up with anything they would not put up with anything I mean imagine I imagine if they took four or five accounts like that from each one with their names and they would not like their names to be put on the accounts I do not know not a
sus nombres en las cuentas no sé ni de
[ __ ] joke or a [ __ ] joke I mean but
[__] coña ni de [__] coña o sea pero
trust you here what he has given me by
fíate tú aquí de lo que me ha metido by
the
the
face I mean imagine this man in the
face o sea imaginaros este hombre en el
trial eh in the trials what does
juicio eh en los juicios qué tiene que
Javi have to do with it here he is already being a coward he
ver Javi aquí ya esl ser un [__] ya
is already brave laser enjoy the
está valiente láser disfruta las
lawsuits bro I do not know what you want me to
demandas bro no sé que quieres que te
tell you he is brave
diga él es un valiente
enjoy Well if you are brave let's see if you take the let's see if you
disfruta Pues si eres un valiente a ver
take and appear
si coges el a ver si coges y te personas
in the lawsuit lerl that you already have it
tú en la demanda lerl que la tienes ya
eh It happens that now apparently it has
eh Pasa que ahora por lo visto se ha
moved and now he doesn't take it now he
mudado y ahora tampoco la coge ahora se
has moved now the player will have to see
ha mudado ahora el jugado tendrá que ver
where he has moved I mean he keeps putting it
a dónde se ha mudado O sea no para de
off buddy e Well I imagine he will have to appear in
alargarla colega e Bueno me imagino que
person at the D prison
se tendrá que personar en la penal del D
and there we will catch him you know or
y por ahí lo trincar remos sabes o se la
Pablo will send it directly to
mandará Pablo directamente a la
his attorney or something because
procuradora suya o alguna cosa porque
come on I've been suing him since May
vamos ya hace que lo demandé desde mayo
and I'm looking forward to the first one Let him
y estoy deseando que pase la primera Que
answer the first one because I'm going to
responda la primera porque le voy a
file a second one and Dallas too Dallas
poner una segunda y Dallas también
too I don't know if it's that he doesn't care
Dallas también yo no sé si es que le da
if he gets the defense for
igual si es que le sale la defensa
free or if he considers that with these
gratis o él considera que con estas
explanations I don't know the truth are things
explicaci No lo sé la verdad son cosas
that I don't understand eh they are things that I don't
que no entiendo eh son cosas que no
understand no but there is a moment like I don't
entiendo no pero hay un momento como no
know if it's in the in the debate like he
sé si es en el en el debate como que le
threw in Uncle Shur that Uncle
echó en cara al tío shur que el que el
Shur didn't want didn't want to be
tío shur no quería no quería ser
sued or something like that he threw in
demandado o sea algo así le echó en cara
Uncle Shur yes he remains like
al tío shur sio se queda así como
Hello What was it I mean the guy
Hola Qué es lo que fue O sea que el tío
is is
está está eh
slandering with full knowledge eh I
difamando con pleno conocimiento eh o
mean with it is not a  criticism of those on the
sea con no es una crítica a los de la
talk show is just that the hate they're
tertulia es solo que el hate que están
receiving is nothing Compared to what
recibiendo no es nada Comparado a lo que
Javi receives no no no no way so it
Javi recibe no no no ni de [__]
seems pretty
coña así que me parece bastante
absurd to me but oh well if a
absurdo pero bueno si le hace feliz una
civil suit makes him happy go ahead, where is it
demanda civil adelante me dónde es
dude maybe put it up as announced
tío a lo mejor poner de anunciado
don't file a complaint get serer to waste
no denuncia meter a serer a perder el
lawyers' time Oh I don't remember it
tiempo a abogados a Ah no me acuerdo es
was the talk show that was like that
que fue la tertulia que fue como
You may also be aware that you
eso Tú igual estás consciente de que
could receive a
podrías recibir una denuncia por
defamation complaint or not I mean it depends let's see it
difamación o no O sea depende a ver
depends because yes yes no it is with a lot of
depende porque si si no es con mucho
contempt with Reckless contempt the
desprecio con Temerario desprecio la
truth is in theory not
verdad en teoría no ha quedado absuelto
many people have been acquitted then As long as he is there I
mucha gente entonces Mientras esté el Yo
think he is an abuser and he is not an
creo que es un maltratador y no es un
abuser noom no then we play around no no no
maltratador noom no entonces jugamos por
no but his lyrics said it
ahí no no no no pero lo ha dicho su
the truth is no I don't like receiving
la verdad es que no no me Mola recibir
complaints then not even that move bro that's why
denuncias luego ni esa movida bro por
I'm not going to tell you dasas he is a
eso yo no te voy a decir dasas es un
groomer you
groomer
know oh you don't like it either it's that there it is there is
sabes a tampoco te Mola es que ahí
the
est ahí está la
question That's where sometimes
cuestión Ahí es donde cuando a veces
I talk about morals that he says that I  I say that I
hablo de moral que dice que yo digo que
am a moralist and I have said that I have never
soy moralista y yo he dicho que nunca he
been a moralist in fact I consider that
sido moralista de hecho considero quea
morality is a mistake everyone has it
moral es un error todo el mundo la tiene
but relying on morality seems repulsive to me
pero apoyarse moral me parece repulsivo
when you want to be right about that issue
cuando quieres tener razón con ese tema
but obviously we all have
pero obviamente todos tenemos principios
moral principles and unfortunately my
morales y por desgracia mis principios
moral principles and my ethics make it
morales y mi ética hacen que esté por
above telling the truth about what I believe
encima decir la verdad de lo que creo
above the fear and the [ __ ] of
por encima del miedo y la cagona de de
a complaint that they can file against me when there are
una denuncia que me puedan poner cuando
enough ind bu I mean what are
hay ind suficientes bu O sea qué buscas
you looking for do you think Dallas and Javi Oliveira
vos crees que Dallas Y Javi oliveira se
leave the internet that is your end let's
vayan de internet ese es tu fin a
see I don't remember but wait a moment I'm not
ver no me acuerdo pero un momento que no
going to look for it because we're going to waste
lo voy a buscar porque vamos a perder
time but there was a moment
tiempo pero hubo un momento como que
like he told uncle shur Ah pu
como que él le dijo al tío shur Ah pu
what happens is that you don't want to
que tú lo que pasa es que no quieres
receive a complaint and uncle sh says
recibir denuncia y le dice el tío sh
man of course I mean you can expose and you
hombre claro o sea tú puedes exponer y
can say everything you want without
puedes decir todo lo que tú quieras sin
defaming Of course of course I mean it's not I mean what
difamar Claro claro o sea no es o sea lo
he wants to normalize but only
que él quiere normalizar pero solo
when it's him who is being sued Okay
cuando es a él al que se la ponen Vale
when it's the others who are being
cuando somos los demás a lo mejor a los
sued for insulting or for I don't
que nos demandan por insultar o por no
know what okay  It's for expressions that
sé qué vale que es por expresiones que
are very different, I mean, a lawsuit for the
es muy diferente o sea una demanda por
right to honor, it can be
derecho a honor puede
for insults. I mean, have you seen what
por insultos O sea ya visteis lo que son
the lawsuits they've filed against me are, hair
las demandas que me han puesto a mí pelo
broom, I don't know what, or the one from Nauter? No, the one they
escoba no sé qué o la de nauter No la
filed against Nauter, you bastard,
que le pusieron a nauter cabronazo
[ __ ], I don't know what you know, no, no, no, very different,
[__] no sé qué sabes no no no muy
it's what you say every day,
diferente es lo que tú dices cada día
my son, very, very,
hijo mío muy muy muy diferente que si
very different, what if he's an abuser, what if he's a groomer, what if he's not. I mean, very different, do you understand me
sea muy diferente me entiendes
and he wants to normalize
y y él quiere normalizar como
like, like, it's not like that's him for
que como que no es que eso es el por
telling the truth, like what what. I mean, I really don't
decir la verdad cómo
understand, eh. I don't understand because he's already
entiendo eh No lo entiendo porque ya él
signed that he's going to continue
como que ha firmado que lo va a seguir
doing it and that and that he doesn't care about the
haciendo y que y que le da igual las
lawsuits and all that stuff, okay. So,
demandas y todo el rollo ese vale Así
nothing, you keep going with those expressions
que nada tú sigue con esas expresiones
every day and we're
todos los días y nosotros todos los días
going to sue you every day, I mean, there's no
te vamos a demandar o sea es que no hay
more, we don't have a lawyer there who
más tampoco tenemos un abogado ahí que
already has us made, let's say he's missing
que nos tiene ya hecho vamos le falta ya
the flat rate,
la tarifa plana
no, but if you want to, that's why
no pero es que si quier es eso porquees
you could express yourself in another way
tú te podrías expresar de otra manera a
when you think  I don't know who's
la hora tú piensas que no sé quién tiene
right Well, you can express it in a
razón Bueno pues tú puedes expresarlo de
way that doesn't violate
manera que no vulner el honor de la
people's honor, you know, but well, level. This one is okay. I do
gente sabes pero bueno nivel Este vale
n't know who the [ __ ] Cris Chan is,
No sé quién [__] es el Cris Chan ese
but I'm sure Dallas is
pero seguro que Dallas es
worse. And that's
peor Y ya
it. If you want to get informed about that, Tommy
está si te quieres informar de eso Tommy
Black has a very complete video about
Black tiene un vídeo muy completo sobre
Christian, well, I'll watch it. I'll watch it
chistian pues lo veré lo
if you're interested, I'll read you. But
veré si te hace ilusión yo te leo pero
then Cristian is a crazy guy. Cristian
entonces Cristian es un loquito Cristian
is a crazy guy and a criminal because he
es un loquito y un delincuente porque él
was in jail. I'm glad. So you don't
estuvo preso me alegro entonces tú no
criticize Dalas. Because Cristian is worse
criticas a Dalas Porque Cristian es peor
because I remind you that that was your
porque te recuerdo que ese fue tu
point and the evidence, Mr.
punto y las pruebas señor
Laser, if you want. I'll put here everything that
laser si quieres Pongo aquí todo lo que
Dallas has done and you call him crazy.
ha hecho dalla y tú le llamas loquito
Haha,
Jaja
man. It's that this man has a
tío Es que este hombre tiene una
lawsuit and a complaint and he's here
demanda y una denuncia y está aquí
saying that a guy who has done what,
diciendo que un tío que ha hecho lo que
what things has this Cristian done? She
qué cosas ha hecho el Cristian este Esa
's in jail, right? What things did
está en la cárcel no Qué cosas hizo
Cris's father do along with Barbara? They are
el padre de Cris junto con Bárbara son
the victims of this story. He threatened to
las víctimas de esta historia amenazó de
kill a boy in his hand because they won
muerte un chico en sumano porque ganaron
a
un
contest. I criticize Dalas whenever he
concurso yo critico a Dalas siempre que
does something wrong, the day he goes to jail I'm going
hace algo mal el día que caiga preso voy
to say that he's a  delinquent as I say
a decir que es un delincuente como digo
with crisan until then he's going to
con crisan hasta entonces me va a
seem like a sicko like everyone else and he says
parecer un enfermito como todos y dice
laser well you can call him a
láser pues ya puedes llamarle
delinquent yes I mean dude turkey is being
delincuente si o sea tío pavo está
sued Eh well you can call him a
demandado Eh pues ya puedes llamarle
delinquent if you want Because failing to comply with a
delincuente si quieres Porque incumplir
Supreme Court ruling is a
una sentencia del tribunal supremo Es
crime point number one I mean what do you
delito punto número uno o sea Tú qué
know if he fails to comply or not he fails to comply with
sabes si lo incumple o no lo incumple
the deadlines that there are I mean
los plazos que hay o sea se tendrá que
an execution will have to be requested and they will have to
pedir una ejecución y y tendrán que
report him they will have to condemn him not a
denunciarlo tendrán que condenarlo no
thousand things but now
mil cosas pero ahora se tiene que hacer
an execution has to be done And then
una ejecución Y entonces se dan unos
deadlines are given but no no he takes it for granted that well okay I already
plazos pero no no él da por hecho que
do it today you you will also
bueno vale Ya lo hago hoy tú tú también
call delinquent people who
llamarás delincuente a la gente que
have a sentence for something and don't
tiene una condena por algo y no la
serve it of course who is it doesn't remind you
cumple claro quién es no te recuerda
of 2017 of a dog that
nada de 2017 de un perrito que
disappeared out of nowhere car that I'm not
desapareció de la nada coche que yo no
asking you if it's okay or not to
te estoy preguntando si está bien o no
comply Estefanía a kiss I mean you
el cumplir Estefanía un beso o sea
want me to talk about a sentence from 2017 I
quieres que hable una sentencia de 2017
mean from 8 years ago of the one that says that
o sea de hace 8 años de la que dice que
laser with us weight short hair and
laser con nos peso corto de pelo y
bathed is Javi Javi from 2000 what André
bañado es Javi Javi del 2000 qué André
please No  jodas
por favor No jodas
says, so you want me to talk about a
dice o sea quieres que hable de una
sentence from 2017, that is, from 8 years ago.
sentencia de 2017 o sea de hace 8 años
Oh well, you can't talk about things from
Ah bueno no se puede hablar de cosas de
8 years ago, okay, about what they say, they say
hace 8 años vale de la que dicen dicen
that the dog was lost and there is still nothing
que el perro se perdió y aún no hay nada
firm. It's strange,
en firme Es raro
no, but that sentence was not carried out, no, they did not
no pero esa sentencia no se cumplió no
return the dog,
no devolvieron al perro
no. And what's relevant about that if there is no
no Y eso que tiene de relevante si no
firm sentence, what do you know?
hay una sentencia en firme que se
And even if they are firm. We will have to
Y aunque estén firme Tendremos que
wait for someone to go to
esperar a que alguien vaya a la
jail. What a
cárcel que
joke, this is, I don't know, it makes no
noada es que esto yo no sé no tiene
sense, look at this. Dallas got on a
sentido mirar este Dallas se subió a una
15-year-old in a hotel, he hit his
de 15 años a un hotel le pegaba a su
dog, he killed his bed, León
perro mató a su cama León maltrataba
psychologically abused Miare, I mean, this is, they're
psicológicamente a miare o sea esto es
going to condemn him. This guy is
es que lo van a condenar Es que este t
going to condemn him now, man, this is
solo ya lo van a condenar tío esto es
a sentence. This guy alone scammed hundreds
una condena este t solo estafó cientos
of thousands of euros from his
de miles de euros a sus
followers. I was wrong. Tommy didn't
seguidores me equivoqué Tommy no le
dedicate a single video to him, he dedicated two parts to him.
dedicó un solo víde le dedicó dos partes
It's that Christian Estela saying that
Es que lo de chistian Estela decir que
Dallas is worse is
Dallas es peor es una
crazy, I don't know the truth. I mean, they want to
locura no sé la verdad O sea lo quieren
censor him, eh, he says, man, what is it?  It's not to
censurar eh dice eh tío que que es que
say Well they're going to sue him No,
no es decir Bueno lo van a demandar No
no, it's not that he's being sued he
no es que está demandado
says I'll play and still there's no way he can
dice tocaré y aún así no hay huevo de
call him groomer directly because of the
decirle directamente groomer por lo de
no, no, the groomer has told him in
no no el groomer sí le ha dicho en en
several parts of the lawsuit there's the
varias partes de la demanda hay lo de
groomer thing he called him pedophile he said
groomer le ha dicho pedófilo le ha dicho
a lot of things I really I mean I don't
un montón de cosas yo de verdad O sea no
understand eh I don't understand look
lo entiendo eh No lo entiendo mira que
I was a camicas eh a long time ago eh
yo era camicas eh hace un montón de años
look I was a camicas eh but that's
eh mira que yo era camicas eh pero eso
already that I mean being already sued
ya es que lo o sea estando ya demandado
eh I don't know man it seems too much even
eh No sé tío me parece demasiado incluso
for him I don't know if he's thinking of leaving the
para él no sé si es que se piensa ir del
country if he has left the country I don't know the
país si se ha ido del país No lo sé la
truth I don't know I don't know I don't
verdad no
know I'm trying to find
sé No lo sé No lo sé intento encontrar
a logic of why someone would act like that
una lógica de Por qué alguien actuaría
but I don't know you talk about Education look at yourself
así pero no lo sé hablas de Educación
How you talk to others Pablo
mírate Cómo hablas a los demás Pablo
This other one not exposing criminals eh And
Este otro no exponiendo criminales eh Y
Dalis Veira they say You know that this year
dalis veira dicen Tú sabes que este año
is your lucky day we already have evidence
es tu día de suerte ya tenemos evidencia
of how you bribed judges so that
de cómo sobornaste a jueces para que
Dallas and Javi win
gane Dallas Y Javi
No, it's not that neither I in my time nor
No no es que ni yo en mi época o sea ni
I in my  hater era in my time when I was crazy, I had
yo en mi época hater en mi época que se
no control, I didn't
me iba la olla que no controlaba no
even know that lawsuits existed,
sabía que existían ni siquiera las
eh, I mean, that civil, that
demandas eh o sea yo eso civ eso de que
civil and criminal law existed, that you could
existía civil penal eso de que se podía
sue for insults and all that, I didn't
demandar por insultos y demás yo no
know that existed. I remember that a
sabía que existía Yo me acuerdo que un
neighbor once insulted a doctor, I don't
vecino una vez insultó a un médico no me
remember how angry he got with a
acuerdo que cabreo se cogió con un
doctor at a consultation and the doctor
médico en una consulta y el médico lo
insulted him and no, the doctor reported him and
insultó y no el médico lo denunció y le
paid him, he had to pay him 50 or something like that, I don't
pagó le tuvo que pagar 50 o algo así no
remember what it was, I mean, I remember
me acuerdo que fue o sea yo me acuerdo
that people here have been reported for
que aquí se ha denunciado gente por
insults in the past and it seemed like it never
insulto antiguamente y con como que no
got anywhere, I don't know what you know, I
llegaba a nada nunca no sé qué sabes
had that trial with the crazy guy here
tuve el juicio aquel con el loquito aqu
who told me that I'm going to split you in
que me dijo lo de te voy a partir por la
half. Do you remember, failing to comply with a
mitad Te acuerdas incumplir una
sentence for insults is a
sentencia por insultos es un delito
serious crime, so nothing Dallas you We'll have to
grave pues nada Dallas te Tendremos que
send you to the cecot with in El Salvador, right? It's
mandar al cecot con en El Salvador verd
not that it's serious or not serious It's
No es que sea grave ni no grave Es una
something that you can't do, you can't
cosa que no no se puede hacer no se
fail to comply with a sentence and I don't
puede incumplir una sentencia y yo no
count I hope d doesn't get over it
cuento Espero que d no se le vaya a
off the top of my head, from the
pasar por la cabeza vamos yo por las
times I've spoken to him about this
veces que yo he hablado con él de ese
subject, he has never once
tema a mí en ningún momento me ha
told me that he's not going to pay, he will
ensinado de que no lo vaya a pagar lo
pay, he will put the four screenshots of the
pagará pondrá las cuatro capturas de la
sentence, that is, the ruling in four
sentencia o sea el fallo en cuatro
videos Random and off he's not going to No, not to
vídeos Random y fuera no va a No a no
comply with a sentence, those who have
cumplir una sentencia los que han
breached a sentence are the others
incumplido una sentencia son los otros
no But it's that no no no it doesn't matter it doesn't
no Pero es que no no no que da igual que
matter Well the thing here is that now
igual Bueno aquí la movida es que ahora
today is to doubt that Fran has the
lo de hoy es dudar de que Fran tenga la
disease okay today they have suddenly
enfermedad vale hoy de repente han
started to doubt that
empezado a dudar de que
this one has which by the way I also
de que este tenga que por cierto también
have several clips they have already sent it to me
tengo varios clips ya me lo han mandado
this afternoon of him denying the disease
esta tarde de ese negando la enfermedad
I went back to Valeria simply because of
yo me volvich a Valeria simplemente por
these absurd reasonings of these
estos razonamientos absurdos de esta
other people and of course your accent is
otra gente y claro tu acento no tiene
artless s or he supports Grandpa a handsome kiss
arte s o el apoya Abuelo un beso guapo
e Hey, with this nonsense we've had 12
e Oye pues con la tontería llevamos 12
out of 50
de 50
eh Fran's hair is falling out because of the heat
eh se le cae el pelo a Fran por el calor
in Thailand Yes I can imagine but it's
de Tailandia Sí me imagino pero es
tremendous it's tremendous
tremendo es tremendo
man it's
tío es
tremendous Fran's extreme suffering is back
tremendo vuelve el sufrimiento extremo
cua What do you think of the supposed supposed
cua Qué piensas del supuesto supuesto
cancer  of Fran man there are pictures of Fran at
cáncer de Fran tío hay fotos de Fran con
30 years old without hair already with the treatment
30 años sin pelo ya con el tratamiento
eh There are pictures of Fran on the internet from
eh Hay fotos de Fran en internet de
when he wasn't famous with the treatment
cuando no era famoso con el tratamiento
man since when he wasn't famous not
hombre desde cuando no era famoso no de
from 15 years before being
de 15 años antes de ser
famous the story of Chris Chan is
famoso la historia de Chris Chan es
much more extensive than that of Spartacus and
mucho más extensa que la de Espartaco y
the one of the donber gets together I recommend it
la del donber se junta se la recomiendo
to the people in the
a la gente del
chat Well I don't know but to treat it
chat Pues no sé pero ya para tratarlo
we no no no no no no How did
nosotros no no no no pilla
my paloma go on she just
no Cómo siguió mi paloma me acaba de
answered me on WhatsApp right now she
contestar whatapp ahora mismo me ha
told me that H has been
dicho que regulín H me le ha estado
giving me a fever and all that but well, occupational jinx she
dando fiebre y eso pero bueno gafes del
told me wait I'm going to tell her if she
dicho espérate le voy a decir que si
wants to tell us
quiere decirnos
something okay we're here live and and
algo vale estamos aquí en directo y y la
people are asking about you do you want to
gente está preguntando por ti quieres
send an audio to people or what And
mandarle un audio a la gente o qué Y
tell her like How are you
dile como Cómo
caela How are you Damn
estás caela Cómo estás [__] me está
a lot of people are talking to me for gua What's up with
hablando un montón de gente por gua Qué
that guy Nacho when the
pasa ese sujeto Nacho cuando pasó el
chicken thing happened he made a super
tema de pollo te hizo un vídeo super
disgusting video that he deleted and then he got into a fight with
asqueroso que borró y luego se peleó con
her and he made a disgusting video of
ella y le hizo un vídeo asqueroso a
her let's
ella a
see but I understand that people  no no
ver pero yo entiendo que la gente no no
converge In my opinion because sometimes
converja En mi opinión porque a veces a
maybe I give a bad explanation I
lo mejor doy una explicación mala me
express myself badly or I'm very radical or
Expreso mal o soy muy radical o lo que
whatever but what do you want me to say I can't
sea pero yo Qué quieres que te diga no
stop thinking that
puedo dejar de opinar
because if you are a
eso pues si eres un
communicator your job as a
comunicador tu labor como
communicator is to communicate well not to communicate
comunicador comunicar bien no comunicar
badly you know I mean you are a
mal sabes O sea tú eres creador de
content creator or whatever you want to call yourself
contenido o como te quieras llamar
within
dentro de
functions the most important is to communicate
funciones la más importante es comunicar
and you communicate badly as a
y comunicas mal siendo
communicator Well let's see I still have
comunicador Pues a ver yo sigo teniendo
contacts at Foster where I
contactos en el Foster donde yo
used to work if you
antiguamente si
want If you want I can ask something
quieres Si quieres puedo preguntar
else no I mean I don't think he barely gets paid from
otra cosa no O sea no creo que cobre de
YouTube Noa I don't think he makes a living from
YouTube apenas Noa No creo que viva de
YouTube he couldn't have had a time
YouTube no pudo haber tenido una época
because in one of the videos of the
porque en una en uno de los vídeos de la
lawsuit they are also posted because he
demanda además están puesto porque el
boasts about what he earns in the lawsuit at
presumen de lo que gana en la demanda en
the time of the videos of the lawsuit
la época de de los vídeos de la demanda
he boasts about what he earns because there was
el presume de lo que gana porque yo hubo
one time when I told him dude this
una vez que le dije tío le interesa este
guy is interested in everything he's doing And where is he getting into you
tío todo lo que está haciendo Y dónde se
know and there's a video where he insults me
sabes y él hay un vídeo donde me insulta
for a change and says if you knew what
para variar y dice si supieras lo que
I earn I don't know what I don't know how much And then
gano no sé qué no sé cuánto Y entonces
a person told me he told me what he
me dijo una persona me dijo lo que
earned is not  a lot but well it was to
ganaba no es mucho pero bueno era para
live but of course
vivir pero claro
now I don't know what this is Now you know
ahora no sé esto que son Ahora sabes
100 I don't
100 no
know the truth But well if it's worth it
sé la verdad Pero bueno si le merece la
this is tremendous okay of course then they
esto es tremendo vale claro entonces e
're messing with Fran cua okay because of
se estn metiendo con Fran cua vale por
the subject this over here look
el tema este por aquí mira vuelve el
Fran's extreme suffering comes back cap
sufrimiento extremo de Fran gorra para
backward this is ler no cap backward
atrás este es ler no gorra para atrás
sleeveless shirt and victimhood it
camiseta sin manga y victimismo me
seems to me that I've seen this related to
parece que esto lo he visto relaciona a
Dallas I mean what the hell does
Dallas O sea qué [__] tiene que ver el
Fran's video have to do with Dallas no and asking for
vídeo de Fran con Dallas no y pedir
money no don't forget they always ask for money
dinerito no no te olvides siempre piden
they're
dinerito son
leeches plural
sanguijuelas plural
Fran is not asking for money in this
Fran no está pidiendo dinero en esto
okay Ah Wait there was another one I mean How to
vale Ah Espera que había otro o sea Cómo
mix I don't think it's a good idea for you to make
mezclar no creo que sea buena idea que
a Chris Chan video since the
hagas un video de Chris Chan ya que la
story is very burned But it would be
historia está muy quemada Pero estaría
good if the reactions together with the
bien que las reacciones junto con la
community of
comunidad de
X reactions we could do no and we're going to
X reacciones podríamos hacer no y vamos
do the I'll
a hacer de lo
tell you thing about Spartacus and all
de te lo diré de lo de Espartaco y todo
that no well let's see we have them
eso no bueno a ver las tenemos
pending
pendientes
eh damn there was a
eh [__] había un
tweet I don't remember which one dude
tweet no me acuerdo de cuál de
the
ellos tío el tet de San
Valentine's Day tet Happy Valentine's Day
Valentín Feliz día del amor y la
how terrible to mess with
amistad qué terrible meterse así con
Frank like this there was a  TT this morning relate
Frank había un TT esta mañana relacioná
me to the
a mí con lo del tema de
Fran thing too, I mean
la de Fran también o sea
eh A viral thing is happening in the world Okay
eh Pasa una cosa viral en el mundo Vale
and it's Javi's fault, I mean they bring up
y la culpa es de de Javi o sea meten a
Javi Dallas because they
Javi Dallas por la
bring up Javi Dallas but come on eh
cara meten a Javi Dallas pero vamos eh
Because yes but I don't remember what account it
Porque sí pero no me acuerdo qué cuenta
was It was an account of this one too it was
era Era una cuenta de esta también era
an account that said that eh well
una cuenta como que decía que Eh bueno
that Fran now has some complaints and
que Fran Ahora tiene unas querellas y
that I had earned money last year
que yo había ganado dinero el año pasado
when when when the sanctuary thing I don't
cuando cuando cuando lo del santuario no
know something like that it said that it's like I mean it's
sé algo así ponía que es como o sea es
like the typical one of like they're not going to
como la típica de a que no van a
relate Dallas and Javi with
relacionar a Dallas y a Javi con lo de
Francua with Francua's dear hold
francua con las querida de francua
me The cubata Okay and here gibel was
sujétame El cubata Vale y aquí gibel se
surprised No look, to me The pelucas did
sorprendía No mira que a mí El pelucas
n't seem bad to me in the debate kid but
en el debate no me pareció mal pibe pero
if it's that you don't need for him to seem
si es que no necesitas que te parezca
nice to you talking for 10 minutes gibel I mean no no
simpático 10 minutos hablando gibel
no that a person
O sea no no no que una persona te
seems nice to you talking for 10 minutes
parezca agradable hablando 10 minutos
what sense dude is a person they're
que qué sentido tío es una persona son
all of them okay they're all
todos ellos vale son todos ellos
people who dedicate themselves every day to
personas que se dedican cada día a
stalking they get up  in the morning they
stalkear se levantan por la mañana
check your social Blade to see if you
revisan tu social Blade para ver si tú
've deleted a video insults
has borrado un vídeo insultos
accusations of crimes they're looking for your
imputaciones de delitos buscan a tu
family they're looking for everything or rather the javil
familia buscan todo o sea el javil
peluca posted a TT the other day also about
peluca puso un TT el otro día también de
Dallas's mother I don't know if he searched in I do
la madre de Dallas no no sé si buscó en
n't know what company that Dallas's mother had that's
no sé qué empresa que tenía la madre de
all remember when they put
Dallas es todo acordaros cuando pusieron
there they started to dox an
ahí empezaron a a doxear a una mujer
anonymous woman that they thought was Ana
anónima que se pensaban que era la Ana
Ana this lady from space I mean it
la Ana la señora esta de los space o sea
's 24
es 24
hours How come I didn't think the guy was bad
horas Cómo que no me pareció mal el tipo
but putting into doubt such a
pero poner en duda una enfermedad tan
horrible disease and that you can see from kilometers away the
horrible y que se ve a Kilómetros el
damage it does to Franco in the
daño que le hace a Franco en el
treatment is one of the most nefarious things I've
tratamiento es de las cosas más nefastas
seen is that
que vi es que
gibel but if you already knew man if he was a
gibel pero si ya lo sabías tío si era
follower of mine on many occasions
seguidor mío en muchas ocasiones ha
gibel has commented a lot of things about
comentado gibel un montón de cosas de
milor man that you put when you got
milor tío que te pusiste cuando te
angry with me to give voice to legum
picaste conmigo a darle voz a legum
pasasa man to deny things that you were in at
pasasa tío a negar cosas que tú estabas
the time and you lived them and you know how they
en la época y las viviste y sabes cómo
were and because of the ardor because of the sting
fueron y por por el ardor por el picor
with me at one point you started to
conmigo en un momento dado te pusiste a
react to a video  of compat I didn't see
reaccionar a un vídeo de compat yo no vi
the reaction I saw that he told me place sab
la reacción vi que me lo dijo lugar sab
but like and it happens to me it's the same a
pero como y yo pasa es lo mismo un
stalker from the group of stalkers I mean there's
acosador del grupo de acosadores o sea
no more I mean there's no more without any
no hay más O sea no hay más sin ningún
kind of trembling when
tipo de temblor al
saying it I mean how are you going to be surprised of
decirlo o sea cómo te vas a sorprender
course I told him but if this that they
claro se lo he dicho pero si esto que
doubt Fran's illness if it's the
duden de la enfermedad de Fran si es lo
least that is dispatched I mean I wish for me
mínimo que se despacha o sea Ojalá a mí
the least the least I wish in this
lo mínimo lo mínimo Ojalá en esta
persecution it would be that
persecución sería que
em I wish the same the least of mine would be that they
em Ojalá lo mismo lo mínimo mío fuera
doubt my illness that I
que que dudaran de la enfermedad mía que
also have a clip from the len laser since they
también tengo clip del láser len ya que
sent them to me today saying eh
me las han mandado hoy diciendo eh que
that I don't have CR that I made it up that it
que yo no tengo CR que me lo he
's like What because I ate
inventado que es como What porque comí
popcorn here I think it was and on another
palomitas aquí creo que fue y en otra
occasion because I drink I don't know what like dude I
ocasión porque bebo no sé qué como tío o
mean within the cron you can be
sea dentro del cron tú puedes estar
better worse in remission in a flare I
mejor peor en remisión en brote O
mean it doesn't make any sense dude these are things
sea no tiene ni sentido tío son cosas
that are things that don't make any
que son cosas que no tienen ni
sense I'm that the fact that
sentido Yo es que que se esté dando
these people are realizing these things now
cuenta ahora esta gente de estas cosas
no I don't understand why I think it's
no no entiendo el Por qué creo que es
because it's happened to them they don't  would
porque les ha tocado a ellos ellos no
they put up with
aguantarían
accounts with
eh cuentas con nombres de ellos
insulting names or with parody names about
insultantes o con nombres parodias sobre
them
ellos
context I was looking exactly
contexto yo estuve viendo exactamente
What is the amount of tweets and what is
Cuál es la cantidad de tweets y cuál es
the amount of Well yes of tweets that
la cantidad de Bueno sí de tweets que
Javiel pelucas posts to Dallas And Javi I have
pone javiel pelucas a Dallas Y Javi lo
calculated it Look this guy has been
he calculado Mirad este Chico lleva
doing it since August when the
haciéndolo desde agosto que se creó la
2000 account was created I
cuenta de 2000
don't understand the calculation either but if
No entiendo el cálculo tampoco pero si
you go in here no and here it will come
es que te metes aquí no y aquí
out let's
saldrá vamos a
see let's see yes already the name the banner the
ver vamos si ya el nombre el banner el
but the thing is that there are people These are kids who
pero es que hay gente Estos son chavales
are special But there are people that I
que son especiales Pero hay gente que yo
know who have an account okay I'll
sé quién tiene alguna cuenta vale que ya
explain it And I am this I'm going to
lo explicaré Y eso lo estoy esto lo voy
prepare for a series on the
a preparar para una serie en el canal
main channel okay there will
principal vale que
be that I'm waiting for something I'm waiting
habrá que estoy esperando una cosa estoy
I'm waiting for some things
esperando Estoy esperando unas cosas
okay to do that series But there are people
vale para hacer esa serie Pero hay gente
that we know and who have accounts with
que conocemos y que llevan cuentas con
my name nicknames nicknames with the same thing that
mi nombre motes apodos con lo mismo que
these kids do you know and of course and they reveal things that
estos chavales hacen sabes y claro y
are private and they
desvelan cosas que son privadas y
reveal things that well but well Javi
desvelan cosas que bueno pero bueno Javi
oliveira this one in particular okay I mean
oliveira la de este en concreto vale o
no man for God's sake there's no way
sea que no hombre por Dios no hay manera
this one puts
este pone
uh  127 tweet Let's see
eh 127 tweet A ver
wait following follower twit
espérate following follower twit
Well look, this person has
Pues mira esta persona ha llegado a
posted 1226 tweets in the same month in
poner en el mismo mes
August
1226 tweets en agosto del
2024 The wigs posted seriously
2024 El pelucas llegó a poner en serio
no no but with all the calmness in the
no no pero con toda la tranquilidad del
world and I'll do one that's going to be for a series
mundo y haré una eso va a para una serie
because there are several topics in each series
porque son varios temas en cada serie
but it is, I mean, the CPI crash is It's
pero es o sea lo del chocas del cpi es
ridiculous, that no no no it doesn't make sense
Es ridículo eso no no no tiene sentido
1226 tet posted a month about me
1226 tet llegó a poner un mes sobre mí
okay when we say 1226 tweet It's not
vale cuando decimos 1226 tweet No es
because I don't know if it was a pass or which of
porque no sé si fue un pasa o cuál de
them was like trying to justify
ellos estaba como intentando justificar
Ah but it's that Javi talked every
Ah pero es que Javi hablaba todos los
day about AR rosito chico arrocito it was a
días de AR rosito chico arrocito era un
viral documentary throughout the Peninsula
documental viral en en toda la Península
eh that an episode was coming out every day
eh que iba saliendo un episodio cada día
and in salvo they were commenting on me every day and
y en salva me iban comentando cada día y
you were talking Okay but it didn't
tú ibas hablando Vale pero no se me
cross my mind the things that that that they
pasaba por la cabeza las cosas que que
put there I mean it's that this is
que que ponen ahí o sea es que esto es
you put on a pair of jeans you put on a pair of
te pones un pantalón vaquero te pones un
jeans and the heel is from a
pantalón vaquero y es el talón es de un
child who sewed it in Africa okay  you
niño que lo cosió en África vale que te
comb your hair with a toupee the fake toupee
peinas con un tupé el tupé de mentira es
is pure illness pure illness I mean they are
es pura enfermedad pura enfermedad o sea
not today's tweets because today Javi
no son twit de hoy pues hoy Javi ha
did a program with Iker Hey I like
hecho un programa con Iker Oye me gusta
the program he did today with Iker Hey
el programa que ha hecho hoy con Iker
well tomorrow I do
oye pues mañana el invitado que ha
n't like the guest he brought Hey well in this
traído no me gusta Oye pues en este
video Javi is right Hey well in
vídeo Javi tiene la razón Oye pues en
this other one no no no no no it's not hating for the sake of
este otro no no no no no es odiar por
hating and it doesn't make sense But yes it is
odiar y no tiene sentido Pero si es que
what I'm telling you I mean the r or the delox
es lo que te digo o sea el r o el delox
okay or anyone talks to us
vale o cualquiera se habla con nosotros
while they talk to us what they
mientras que se habla con nosotros lo
're doing now with Fran okay or
que están haciendo ahora con Fran vale o
with them while they talk to
con ellos mientras que se hablan con
us more or less they have a
nosotros más o menos tienen una
cordiality they harass them and the moment
cordialidad los acosan y en el momento
we fight with them they
que nosotros nos peleamos con
follow them and they adore them they
ellos los siguen y y los adoran lo han
did it with delo and they did it with r I
hecho con delo y lo han hecho con r o
mean what's the point of what they came up with with
sea qué sentido tiene la que dieron con
delox But they have the Twitter accounts
delox Pero ellos las cuentas de Twitter
and all these channels the one they came up
y todos los canales estos la que dieron
with with
con
delox I mean they looked for lords of
delox o sea se se buscaron lores de
delox from the polka era all of
delox de la época de la polca todo el
delox's history every news item every
historial de delox cada noticia cada
comment a forum that  There was about delox they
comentario un foro que había sobre delox
gave credibility to the d SS
le dieron credibilidad a los d SS
connection who are now up to their necks
conecction que ahora están hasta el culo
in complaints that not one has come out to
de denuncias que ni uno ha salido a
comment on that okay those of SS connection
comentar eso vale los de SS connection
are up to their [ __ ] necks in complaints
están de denuncias hasta el [__] culo
but man it was
pero tío hacía
necessary just to see them to
falta solamente con verlos
give them something to think that they are
darles algo para pensar que son personas
trustworthy people or not those of SS connection
de fiar o que no los de SS connection
man we are talking about the guys who
tío estamos hablando de los tipos que se
went viral for the
hicieron virales por el por el vídeo de
mortgage video well and in the
la hipoteca bueno Y en el vídeo de la
mortgage video they are decent in the video the
hipoteca son decentes en el vídeo los de
mortgage guys are
las hipotecas son
decent well even those They didn't care about the
decentes pues hasta esos Les valía la
information that gave them those they didn't
información que eso les daba esos les
care they invited them to their live streams okay about
valían los invitaban a sus directos vale
the scammers delos
de los estafador delos denuncia
collective complaint Dalas fights one night with
colectiva se pelea una noche Dalas con
delo because delo decides that he can't stand
delo porque delo decide que no aguanta
the pressure of
más la presión de est
being here anymore and they close the doors of the
de estar aquí y le cierran puertas de la
elite and so on let's know go to
élite y demás vamos sabes
hell already delo is what
e a tomar por culo ya delo es lo
we defend him he whitewashed and all that stuff okay
defendemos lo blanque y todo el rollo
raed of everything ra of everything ra is an
raed de todo ra de todo ra es una
objectively violent person I mean he is
persona objetivamente violenta o sea es
an objectively criminal no
una persona objetivamente delincuente no
no you can't have doubts about sides no This
no puedes tener dudas de bando no Esto
is like this or I don't like him because no no no no it's not
es así o me cae mal porque no no no no
what gives Well then RAE stops
es que da Bueno pues RAE se deja de
talking to us and they support ra
hablar con nosotros y apoyan a ra
yan planas at 4 in the morning in the
yan planas a las 4 de la mañana en el
chat it's brutal in the SS chat
chat es que es brutal en el chat de SS
with it is brutal it's
con es que es brutal es
brutal it's that they have no coherence it doesn't
brutal es que no tienen coherencia no
make sense None of you
tien sentido Ninguno me
understand me 23 So we're talking
entiendes 23 Entonces estamos hablando
about August September October November
de agosto septiembre octubre noviembre
December It's 5 months of one month the 12
diciembre Son 5 meses de un mes los 12
of the other and the two months that we've been
del otro y los dos meses que llevamos
here okay this makes 19
por aquí vale esto hacen 19
months 19 months by Med of one to c tweets
meses 19 meses por Med de un a c tweets
the average is 2.5 okay
que la media es un 2,5 vale
eh And well obviously before 19 by 30
eh Y Bueno evidentemente antes 19 por 30
which would give us the number of days No well
que nos daría la cantidad de días No
then we're going to do the following
pues entonces vamos a hacer la siguiente
calculation 19 by 30 is
cuenta 19 por 30 son
570 by 2.5 we would be talking about that Javi
570 por 2,5 estaríamos hablando que Javi
El pelucas has posted
El pelucas ha puesto de forma
consecutively
consecutiva
eh consecutively I think it failed only TR
eh consecutiva creo que falló solo TR
days from what the person in
días por lo que me comentó la persona
charge of verifying it told me eh
que se encargó de verificarlo eh
1425 tweets Asia Dallas And Javi what's going on what's
1425 tweets Asia Dallas Y Javi qué va qu
going on what's going on 4000 puts it here look Oh no
va qu va 4000 lo pone aquí mira Ah no
These are followers  twit are 7400 dude sh
Estos son followers twit son 7400 tío sh
Look There are days that are 33 tweets There are days
Mira Hay días que son 33 tweet Hay días
that are 10 There are days that are 18
que son 10 Hay días que son 18
24 or so
24 o sea
7300 t dude
7300 t colega
7300 t what the [ __ ] Yeah all about me only
7300 t qué [__] Sí todo sobre mí solo
eh about me Dallas
eh sobre mí Dallas
eh I mean it doesn't make any [ __ ] sense we're
eh o sea que no tiene [__] sentido lo
going to justify this but let's go by
vamos justificar esto pero vamos por
none of the by none of the in any
ninguna de las por ninguna de las de
way I mean but in
ninguna de las formas o sea pero de
no
ninguna de las
way in any way
formas de ninguna de las formas
eh
eh
7300 tweets
7300 tweets
Well that account is D veira
Bueno pues esa cuenta es la de D veira
asendado it's the one that are pure stalkers there's
asendado es la de son puros acosadores
no more worth
no hay más vale
1425 tweets come on right now they're here
1425 tweets vamos ahora mismo están aquí
look I'm going to go into any of the
mira me voy a meter en cualquiera de las
accounts and I would be surprised not to find that they
cuentas y me extrañaría no encontrarme
're clicking on this
con que están poniendo click de este
very live look
propio directo mira
Eh well Wilson is one of the accounts
Eh bueno Wilson es una de las cuentas
that we know Who owns it
que sabemos De quién
and here you have it Twitter no that
es y aquí lo tenéis Twitter no que
was like war with with the here you have it they're right now
estaba como la guerra con con la aquí lo
watching this
tenéis están ahora mismo viendo este
live they're right now watching this
directo están viendo ahora mismo este
live and e
directo y e
the sa but apart
el sa pero aparte
Look jav oliveira is playing dumb and  He says he
Mira jav oliveira se hace el loco y dice
knows nothing about cats. I mean, fate
que no sabe nada de las gatas O sea fate
what he translates to. This is worth it. And he says
tú a lo que traduce Esto vale Y dice
this: this is one who is here to debate
este este es uno que estó aquí a debatir
and here it was one of the most
y aquí fue uno de los debates más
pathetic debates in life,
patéticos de la vida
okay, he knows perfectly well the
vale él sabe perfectamente los
different groups that there are in x
diferentes grupos que hay en x
related to
relacionados con
him that nobody believes them anymore, really, I mean, they
él que nadie se las cree ya de verdad o
are people. Well, right now
sea son personas Bueno pues ahora mismo
you get into each account, they are so much
tú te metes en cada cuenta están tando
about the
sobre el
Direct and thank goodness he said he did it
Direct y menos mal que dijo que lo hacía
for entertainment. But if he has to
por entretenimiento Pero si tiene que
hate the supposed entertainment,
aborrecer el supuesto entretenimiento
These are serious problems that should be
Estos son problemas serios que deberían
dealt with in professional places, there is no way
de tratarse en sitios profesionales hay
for anyone. There is no way,
hay for for de ninguno No hay forma de
since August, the Wilson thing has to be taken
desde agosto lo de Wilson hay que
out. You pass it on, we need to tie up one
sacarlo lo pasais que nos falta atar una
thing that I don't understand, but about Wilson,
cosa que no me llega pero lo de Wilson
I think it's clear. There is not much, there are
yo creo que está claro No hay mucho hay
many things from 2023, but it is very
muchas cosas del 2023 pero es muy
shameful, eh, it is very shameful until
vergonzoso eh es muy vergonzoso hasta
February
febrero del
2025, my approach to this is this
2025 mi planteamiento de esto es este
guy is obsessed or is sick, and a
tío está obsesionado o está malito e una
person who gets up. I mean, no, it is not to
persona que se levanta O sea no no es
say. It is not that Rosio Carrasco, it is that
decir No es que rosio Carrasco es que es
the issue is that  rosio Carrasco today comes out
el tema es que rosio Carrasco hoy sale
in reading Today he goes and sits down and talks about
en lectura Hoy va y se sienta y habla de
his daughter today he talks about no no no no no no no
la hija hoy habla de no no no no no no
this person can I go to
no esta persona ya me puedo ir yo a
Thailand for three weeks okay for the three
Tailandia tres semanas vale que las tres
weeks he's breastfeeding every day from
semanas está cada día teteando pues de
an old cli of Javi's or he takes a cli
un cli antiguo de Javi o te coge un cli
a clipping that someone has fancied who
un recorte que se le ha antojado a
has come to him privately and
alguien que le ha venido por privado y
said Hey look deny this from
le ha dicho Oye mira desmiente esto de
2018 and he takes it and I mean not a
año 2018 y él lo coge y lo O sea no una
person who gets up is going to bed
persona que se levante es acuesta
thinking about a person they don't know is not
pensando en una persona que no conoce no
healthy is not healthy and all for free
es sano no es sano y todo gratis
Exactly he is not a healthy person but
Exactamente no es una persona sana pero
come on no way can he argue
vamos ni de [__] coña puede argumentar
that this is not entertainment no no
que esto es no un entretenimiento no no
no man you have a each and every one of
no hombre tú tienes un todos y cada uno
those who carry the Wilson thing is not
los que llevan el lo del Wilson no es
healthy either the Wilson thing It is evident
sano tampoco lo del Wilson Es evidente
that he is a person who was
que es una persona que quedó
traumatized
traumada
okay But this you get up and say I'm going to
vale Pero esto te levantas y dices voy a
see Javi I'm going to watch all of Javi's videos I'm
ver a Javi voy a ver todo los vídeos de
going to see you know bad bad bad
Javi voy a ver sabes chungo chungo
and dangerous you know what happened to the one from
chungo y peligroso sabéis lo que le pasó
Los  Beatles It's not what I said I
al de Los Beatles No es lo que dije lo
repeat it and it's truly not a car
repito y verdaderamente no es un carro
that I'm going to get off of
del que yo me baja me vaya a bajar
sincerely mana let's go whoever defends
sinceramente mana vamos el que defienda
And justifies this is that it's the same and those
Y justifi esto es que es lo mismo y los
who talk to Those accounts are the
que se hablen con Esas cuentas son los
same there's no more I mean there's no more No no no there's no
mismo no hay más O sea no hay más No no
way you can say Well but it's
no hay forma de tú decir Bueno pero es
a no no no no no for God
que es una no no no no no por Dios
man no for God
hombre no por Dios
that I don't even know give me an
que ni siquiera que no sé poneme un
example of a hater give me an example of
ejemplo de un hater poneme un ejemplo de
a Twitter hater someone not even if it's
un hater de Twitter alguien ni si es que
no it's not
no no es
normal I can't think of an account
normal que no se me ocurre una cuenta
like that they're people you
así son son personas
know a Ricky a Ricky who has a a a
sabes un Ricky un Ricky que tiene una
personal problem with me and a
una un problema personal conmigo y un
personal problem with Dallas I already
problema personal con Dallas yo ya
consider that Ricky is a little
Considero que Ricky está un poquito
sick but well Ricky doesn't talk every
malito pero bueno Ricky no habla todos
day about Javi and Dallas
los días de Javi y de Dallas
nor does he wake up and think about Javi thinks
ni se despierta y piensa en Javi piensa
about Dallas watch a watch the whole live
en Dallas ve un ve el directo entero
to see what clip he can time or take out
para ver qué clip puede minutar o sacar
and cut to give it another meaning or
y recortar para darle otro sentido o
manipulate to put a tet so that
manipular para poner un tet para que la
people think that he said something else you
gente piensa que ha dicho otra cosa me
understand I mean it doesn't make sense you go
entiendes O sea no tiene sentido tú vas
creating your content and  you talk about various
creando tu contenido y hablas de varios
topics no and when you talk about that person
temas no y cuando hablas de esa persona
with whom you have a problem well you speak
con quien tienes un problema pues hablas
more negatively you know but this no
más negativamente sabes pero esto no
this doesn't make
esto no tiene sentido
any sense at all I mean for me a person who
ninguno o sea para mí una persona que
dedicates this amount of time this
dedica esta cantidad de tiempo esta
amount of tweets and this amount of
cantidad de tweets y esta cantidad de
insistence is a person for me is
insistencia es una persona para mí es
a minimally obsessed person and
una persona mínimamente obsesionado y
probably a bad person
probablemente una persona malita
and here many things come out like they say Hey
e aquí salen muchas cosas como dicen Oye
so nauter is bad or or I don't know
pues entonces nauter es malito o o no sé
what Or I don't know how much
qué O no sé cuánto
m now we're going to develop
m vamos ahora ir desarrollando
okay this is like a quota you see
vale esto es como como una cuota viste
I have to come and start saying
yo tengo que venir y empezar a decir
first of all gas is a [ __ ]
primero que que nada gas es un chupapija
And Javi a dog has to say it at the
Y Javi un perro tiene que decirlo al
beginning he has to say it at the beginning
principio tiene que decirlo al principio
okay come on so they stay
vale venga para que se queden
[Laughs]
[Risas]
calm down we start the live with the
tranquilos arrancamos el directo con la
quota we don't start the quota now we continue now we continue now we
cuotita no arrancamos la cuota ahora
continue last video defending jav
seguimos último vídeo defendiendo a jav
peluca saying that there's nothing wrong with
peluca diciendo que no tiene nada malo
putting up a lot of someone's tits Zac richel
poner muchos tets de alguien Zac richel
critic is a person who comes here
crítico es una persona que se pone aquí
to call me at 4 in the morning I
a llamarme a las 4 de la mañana me
remember I was with the
acuerdo Yo que estaba con el
baby that night I had I don't know if I
bebé esa noche se me había no sé si se
had lost sleep or what I was  me like
me había desvelado o qué estaba yo como
falling asleep at 4 in the
durmiéndome a las 4 de la
morning a
mañana una persona
sick person we continue
enferma seguimos
[Music]
[Música]
Check out this last live salsería 2
Mira esto último directo salsería 2
1530 Anyway we're going to
1530 Igual vamos
start reacting to
a ya vamos a empezar a reaccionar a
things the same but today we have a
cosas igual pero hoy tenemos directo
long live if you want a problem to
largo sios quiera problema
go or I mean I didn't have anything prepared
ir o sea no tenía nada preparado
so if someone comes up to talk
entonces pues si alguien sube a hablar
in a cordial manner and such And being
de manera cordial y tal Y pues siendo
an expert or that way in
una persona experta o de esa manera en
animals at least we all know how to express himself
animales menos todos sabemos se expresa
with respect to his friends in the sense that it does
con respecto a sus amigos en el sentido
n't make sense dude was the
de que no tiene sentido tío estaba el
guy Trapped with the four tokens that I
tío Atrapado con los cuatro tokens que
bleach eh now bleached to r
blanqueo eh ahora blanqueado a r
no dude Why is my forehead so
no tío Por qué tengo la frente tan
shiny Why the [ __ ] does it seem like I've
brillante Por qué [__] parece que me he
put ca on my forehead dude I mean I
echado ca en la frente tío o sea os
promise you I haven't done anything or
prometo que no me he hecho nada ni me he
pricked myself or [ __ ] eh I mean what the [ __ ] is
pinchado ni pollas eh O sea qué [__] me
wrong with my forehead no that I'm seeing it
pasa la frente no que me la estoy viendo
super shiny but I realized
superbrillante pero me he dado cuenta
today eh you put oil there's a
hoy eh te echaste aceite no hay una
cream that I make creams to take care of myself
crema que me hago cremas para cuidarme
not the skin and the face and that not
no la la piel y la carita y eso no
when I get out of the shower but e neither that
cuando salgo de la ducha pero e tampoco
I  I showered a lot but I don't understand
que me Duche mucho pero no entiendo el
why my forehead is so shiny
Por qué se se me brilla tanto la frente
like it was the floor of a
como si fuera el suelo de un centro
mall, Javi betrayed me, no,
comercial me traicionó Javi no nunca me
Javi never betrayed me, please donate to the
traicionó Javi por favor donen en el
link that is pinned and throw it away, I need to
link que está fijado y tiren su necesito
recover, it's nothing. Nobody was
recuperarme es que nada Nadie estaba
understanding the crypto thing. But how
entendiendo lo de la cripto Pero cómo
come they weren't understanding the
que no estaban entendiendo lo de la
crypto thing. I mean, how come
cripto O sea cómo que
not with
no con lo
Par, this one was out, no. And what's happening,
de Par este fuera no Y este qué pasa lo
neither of them want it, but Javid, they
quieran ninguno de los dos pero javid
are always a pack, they always go hand in
siempre son un pack siempe van de la
hand. Keep allowing these things,
mano seguir permitiendo estas cosas
keep going like this. Don't you think it's like
seguir tal no creis que es como que
maybe it's unnecessary and maybe it can be
quizás sobra y quizás sí que pod ha
controlled more, eye, eye, we have Paloma's audio,
controlado má ojo ojo tenemos audio de
eh Paloma's audio. Hello Javi,
Paloma eh audio de Paloma Hola Javi
good morning. Well, look, it will take me
Buenos días Pues mira la mano tardaré
about 5 days to regain mobility,
unos 5 días en recuperar movilidad en
that it's functional, and I have to be
que sea funcional y tengo que estar
going to the hospital every day
yendo todos los días al hospital para
for vaccinations, antibiotics and
para vacunaciones para antibióticos y
so on. So, well, all in all,
demás Así que bueno dentro de lo dentro
the best thing is to
de lo bueno lo mejor
worry, okay. And what really
preocuparte vale Y lo que realmente nos
worries us and Slow Lori has
preocupa y el Slow Lori ha
survived,
sobrevivido
I'll see what I can tell you, for me, the
yo s a ver qué puedo decirte para m la
truth is, I
verdad me
papped myself, I'm going to say  see I think that
papee voy decir a ver yo creo
conas no because I think the guy did
que que conas no porque creo que el tipo
go too far but with Javi Alira
sí se mandó las 40 pero con Javi alira
maybe at some point I
puede ser que en algún momento me haya
went too far it could be Gibel maybe at
cevado de más puede ser gibel puede ser
some point
que en algún momento
but in passing eh I mean maybe
sí pero así de pasada eh o sea puede ser
at some point I don't know maybe I'll go over it
que en algún momento no sé a lo mejor lo
and no eh G a kiss a kiss how
repaso y no eh G un beso un beso cómo
are you I'm just from Paloma I don't blame you
estás Soy simp de Paloma no te culpo
Jack I don't
Jack no te
blame you that could be true But well they
culpo eso puede ser verdad Pero bueno
are moments of heat and that's it I don't
son momentos calentura y ya está no lo
take it personally when he messes with me I did
tomó personal cuando él me putea a mí Yo
n't take it personally either because it's something
tampoco lo tomé personal porque es algo
that neither goes nor comes to me I suck
que ni me va ni me viene me chupo
a what Really worries me is that the Slow
un lo que Real preocupa es eso el Slow
loris is doing great I saw it
loris está estupendamente lo he visto
this morning in a tree and I ran away
esta mañana en un árbol y he salo por
because I saw that it was coming down
patas porque he visto que bajaba
and yes yes
y Y sí sí con
carefully How strange How strange that while
cuidadito Qué raro Qué raro que estando
I was
yo
in Thailand it didn't bite me or me
en en Tailandia no me mordiera ni me ni
or sting me anything poisonous eh I mean
me ni me picara nada venenoso eh o sea
the only thing was the last day well the
lo único fue el último día bueno el
last day which was the same day that
último día que era el mismo día que
we took the plane to leave eh in this
cogíamos el avión ya para irnos eh en el
park that  Fran took us to this
parque este que nos llevó Fran el parque
natural park, not a national park, I don't know, I don't know
natural este no nacional no sé no sé
what the park is called. It was a park, a
cómo se llama el parque era un parque un
large natural park where we
parque natural grande
saw the
em que era donde vimos la los
bats, these frogs, do you
murciélagos estos las ranas estas os
remember? And there was one thing that I
acordáis y hubo un eh una cosa que me
love again, grandpa, and so, getting off
buenas de nuevo abuelo y pues saliendo
topic a bit, I'd like to congratulate you on
un poco del tema paso a felicitarte por
the New York blog, tremendous Jewel of
el blog de Nueva York tremenda Joya de
yours, it was definitely worth the wait, I even had a
vos sin duda valió la espera hasta tuve
cameo and everything, although it was really expensive, I
cameo y todo aunque se me hizo carísimo
'd rather go back to Europe another time
prefiero volver a Europa en otra ocasión
than not even for 10 tenths, man, the
que a ni 10 décimos es hombre pues la
truth is that it is a shame because it will
verdad es que sí es una pena porque
surely be a video that I'm
seguramente será un vídeo el que me
surprised that today's one got so many hits, eh. I do
extraña que haya pinchado el de hoy
n't know why it got so many hits
tanto eh No sé por qué ha pinchado tanto
today, I don't know why the one about the Daniel
hoy no sé por qué el de del caso Daniel
Sancho case, but man, what I'm sorry about the
Sancho pero hombre lo que me da pena del
New York video is that it will
vídeo de Nueva York es que que
surely be a video that doesn't get
seguramente será un vídeo que no coja
many views, not on my channel. I don't know, to be
muchas visitas no en mi canal No lo sé
honest, it's a shame because it's cool.
la verdad es una pena porque está chulo
The thing is that there's also the
Lo que pasa es que también cabe la
possibility that it will be a video that as the
posibilidad de que sea un vídeo de que
months, years and so on, it will
con el paso de los meses años y demás sí
get views, okay, or rather, the
vaya viendo visitas vale o sea el
content that I'm always trying to make.
contenido que estoy intentando hacer
on the
siempre en el canal
main channel on purpose sometimes
principal a propósito algunas veces
other times it's not a video that I mean they're
otras veces no es un vídeo que o sea son
videos that never die for example there's
vídeos que nunca mueren por ejemplo hay
a
un
video I mean there are videos that are videos
vídeo O sea hay vídeos que son vídeos
that never die eh I mean they're videos that
que nunca mueren eh o sea son vídeos que
people will always go to check out Look at one
siempre la gente va va a entrar Mira uno
of
de los
this video
de este vídeo
dude this one which is the series The one that puts the
tío este que es la serie El que el que
whole series together is worth it the one that lasts 3
junta toda la serie vale el que dura 3
hours the video is not 3 hours 20 this one that puts the
horas el vídeo no 3 horas 20 este que
whole series together is worth it This video
junta toda la serie vale Este vídeo
got twenty-something thousand views the day I uploaded it I do
pilló el día que lo subí veintitantas
n't know why it got a
mil visitas no sé por qué se pegó un
[ __ ] hit Okay so there it is
palo de la [__] [__] Bueno pues ahí
the video it's almost a year old now and it
está el vídeo tiene ahora casi un año y
has
tiene
300,000 you know so they're
300.000 sabes entonces son son
content that although maybe some
contenidos que aunque A lo mejor algunos
videos fail at the beginning it's not
vídeos pinchan al principio pues no se
ruled out that as the
descarta que conforme van pasando los
days and months go by and so on, they keep
días los meses y demás pues siguen
getting views because no no no
entrando visitas porque no es no no
some are gossip no and so on no
algunos sí son chismes no y demás no
but they're also long ones but they
pero también son lores largos pero no
're not videos about them dying in three days
son vídeos de que mueren a los tres días
like a cat fights with rebor you
como gata se pelea con rebor me
know what I mean and that's what we're trying to
entiendes y es lo que estamos intentando
focus the main channel on
ahí enfocar el canal principal
basically and I think we are
básicamente y creo que lo estamos
getting
consiguiendo
Samara I saw it Says I saw it with my partner
Samara lo vi Dice lo lo vi con mi pareja
and it was brutal I really liked the
y fue brutal a mí me gustó mucho el
block how it turned out the truth is that
block como quedó la verdad es que
eclipse is taking out the cimbrel is right
eclipse se está sacando el cimbrel está
now the editor solo we
ahora mismo el solo de editor
need Editors man see if you
necesitamos Editores tío a ver si me
can contact me shorts editors
podéis contactar editores de shorts
I need an editor who follows the content
Necesito un editor que siga el contenido
of the salsería and telesalseo and
de la salsería y de telesalseo y se
takes care of the daily shorts of both
ocupe de los short diarios de ambos
channels because eh apart I need it to
canales porque eh aparte Necesito que
be a person who follows the
sea una persona que siga bien los
channels well and makes the shorts in the
canales y que haga los short en el
format that the
formato que se hacen los los short de
salsería and telesalseo shorts are made so that they know
salsería y de telesalseo para que sepa
the good moments of the live no or of
los momentos buenos del directo no o de
what we have done during the day a kiss
lo que hayamos hecho en el día un beso
pans the reaction aas against raimito
pans la reacción aas contra raimito
also does not die no no in the salsería
tampoco muere no no en la salsería
even if it is a salseo channel the
aunque sea un canal de salseo la
salsería there are many videos that do not die
salsería hay muchos vídeos que no mueren
eh There are many days that there are many
eh Hay muchos día que que hay muchos
videos that never die eh And that
vídeos que no mueren nunca eh Y que
continue to come in a ton of visits
siguen entrando un montón de visitas
every day or so the truth is that we are
cada día o sea la verdad es que estamos
in a
en un
very sweet moment of youtuber in
momento de de youtuber muy dulce en el
which I can even allow myself to chill
que incluso me puedo permitir chill irme
I could afford to go for a couple of months, I would
Me podría permitir irme un par de meses
probably still be paid, I
seguramente segu seguiría cobrando
think, so I
creo huevo así
had to learn that I'm from the
que tuve que que aprender que soy de la
youth and I'm always going to do it, it's
chavalería y siempre lo voy a hacer é
always going to be a black bull and it's always
siempre va a ser un toro negro y siempre
going to be done by Chaler, per
lo va a hacer chaler per
se, well, yand
si bueno yand
mail with an example, you know, but I'm very
mail con ejemplo sabes pero soy muy
exquisite, uh, I'm very particular because
esquisito eh soy muy especialito porque
I am, I have a lot of OCD in that sense that
soy tengo mucho Toc en ese sentido de
I need that there be a person
que necesito que los que sea una persona
who edits the shorts as the same, as
que edite los short como el mismo como
the same format, no. I mean, that it's the
el mismo formato no O sea que sea el
same, that it's not noticeable that there are several
mismo que no se note que sean varios
Editors, do you think you'll do something? I
Editores vosotros pensáis hacer algo
mean, okay, I wanted you to
quiero decir vale esto quería que
see this very well, Javi, my soul, how
vierais muy bien Javi de mi alma como
are you? 25 months seeing you, I send you
estás Ya 25 meses viendote te mando
greetings from Australia that this and
saludos desde Australia que esto and
to buy a ticket to see
para comprar una entrada para ver a
Drake, a kiss G well I hope I
Drake un beso G pues espero que la
get it, I don't know if you saw this thing, I
consiga no sé si visteis esta movida la
saw it because on Twitter they suddenly
vi porque en Twitter de repente me
notified me that something big had happened on the
avisaron de que había pasado algo gordo
Red Pill live, not on this
en en el directo de red pill no en el
podcast that everyone talks about and
podcast este del Que tanto se habla y
is so controversial, no. I mean, it turns out that
tan polémico es no O sea resulta que de
suddenly I recorded it in case they deleted it
repente lo grabé por si lo borraban
because I say, damn it will be  true at
porque digo [__] será verdad al
first I had my doubts if it was
principio tenía mi duda de que fuera
true or not No, I mean there was a
verdad o no No o sea de que había e un
debate they are there discussing the
debate estn ahí discutiendo sobre el
issue of complaints
tema de las denuncias
and the data not if men hit
e los datos no si los hombres pegan más
women more than women, I mean the
a las mujeres que las mujeres a la o sea
violence and things no And the
las violencias y las cosas no Y la
truth is that this man was
verdad es que el hombre este estaba
eating well with education without
papeando bien con educación sin faltar
disrespect with data okay And suddenly
al respeto con datos vale Y de repente
suddenly something happens that makes
de repente ocurre una cosa que saque a
people feel broken no and I get let's find
la gente como rota no y yo me da vamos
out come people to tweet arm
me enterar ven la gente a twite arme
Javi Javi Get such sentences
Javi Javi Métete tal de condenas
4852 then forgive me but from 199 282
4852 entonces perdonadme pero de 199 282
to 48000 the difference are
a 48000 la diferencia son
innocent they do not get to be resolved Of course
inocentes no llegan a a resolverse Claro
why not because there is no indication of a
porque no porque no hay indicio de
crime that he is an abuser he is
delito de que sea un maltratador es
innocent and maybe we are talking
inocente y a lo mejor estamos hablando
about fraudulent complaints that guy is
de denuncias fraudulentas ese puc da
very cringey the truth is I have never seen
mucho cring la verdad yo no he visto
any of this I have never seen anything I
nunca nada de esto nunca he visto nada o
mean I know that he went to the delox podcast
sea sé que él fue al podcast de delox
to say no Or delos interviewed him no
decer no O delos lo entrevistó no
separation process to stay with
proceso de separación para quedarme con
the  house alimony kick out the
la casa la pensión de alimentos echar al
husband on duty and keep everything is that yes yes yes if
marido de turno y quedarme con todo es
we throw balls to one side we
que si si si echamos valones a un lado
have to throw them to the other women are not
hay que echarlos al otro las mujeres no
beings of light no No not at all, I mean and there's
s seres de luz no No para nada o sea y
everything everywhere that
hay de todo en todos lados eso
obviously we're going to move on to the next
obviamente vamos a pasar a la siguiente
question but first I'm going to read the super
pregunta pero antes voy a leer el super
chat that's there okay I think
chat que hay vale me parece
all of this is extremely important and I
extremadamente importante todo esto y
think that well with all the problems
creo que bueno con todos los problemas
that there have been today let's see Let's
que ha habido hoy a ver
see give me a second I'm going to read the
A ver dame un segundito voy a leer los
Super chats okay I'm going to
Super chats ya vale voy a poner
share the screen give me a second
compartir la pantalla dame un segundo
have you seen that we have integrated the whole
habéis visto que hemos integrado todo el
screen issue is everything fine
tema de la pantalla ya está todo bien
gentlemen balls pass
señores [__] pas
here par par stop the camera camera
aquí par par parar la
the
la
camera the
cámara la
camera happens
cámara pasa
here it looks too real you think it
aquí se ve demasiado real creéis que se
looks too real let's see it depends No
ve demasiado real a ver depende No
man of course it catches you watching the podcast
hombre claro te pilla viendo el podcast
by surprise and it can slip through what happens that of
de sorpresa y puede colar lo pasa que
course it's weird no I mean you start to think
claro es raro no O sea te pones a pensar
and say damn where are they recording what are
y di [__] dónde están grabando queé
they recording with the door open the
están grabando con la puerta abierta la
police no someone comes in
policía no que entre alguien de
suddenly you have Turn off the cameras Turn off
repente habis Apagar las cámaras Apagar
the cameras what a mess what a mess bro
las cámaras qué jaleo qué jaleo hermano
that  already the
esa ya el jaleo
most fake fuss a 240 Claro bill already turns
más falso un billete de 240 Claro ya se
off no and it turns out that
apaga no y resulta que luego por lo
apparently it's fake no good it's fake and now
visto es fake no vale es fake y ahora
later on a while this happens in
más adelante pasa un rato esto en
silence I started recording this the
silencio yo me puse a grabar esto la
screen okay I have it recorded because I
pantalla vale lo tengo grabado porque me
started recording it in case it was something in case it
puse a grabarlo por si era algo por si
was real no And then they deleted the live
era real no Y luego borraban el directo
I don't know I started recording it just in case
yo qu sé me puse a grabarlo por si acaso
okay but
vale pero de
suddenly Good night Javi a
repente Buenas noches Javi un abrazo
huge hug from Chile Hey with this nonsense we've had
enorme desde Chile Oye con la tontería
20 superchats of 50 will we be
llevamos 20 superchat de 50 será que
able to reach 50 today no way
pudiéramos llegar a los 50 hoy ni de
No not a [ __ ] joke no mind you
coña No ni de putísima coña no ojo
[Music]
[Música]
here you've had
aquí ya tuviste
enough masculinity is a
suficiente la masculinidad es una
prison and feminism came to free us
prisión y el feminismo vino a liberarnos
and you retrogrades keep thinking that you
y usted retrógrados siguen pensando que
are necessary that masculinity is
son necesarios que la masculinidad es
necessary that strength is
necesaria que la fuerza es
necessary for years we've lived through
necesaria durante años hemos vivido
operes and
operes y
hoyt
hoyt
CR men will behave
CR los hombres se comportarán
powerfully wear skirts and makeup
potente usarn falda y maquillaje
renounce persona that makes them
renunciar a perona que los hace
hunters
cazadores
warriors you believed it [ __ ] you
guerreros se la creyeron cabrones se la
really believed it  they thought they were going to
creyeron de verdad creyeron que iban a
defeat the bear Uh never never victory
vencer al oso Uh nunca nunca la victoria
is ours Do not let yourselves be
es nuestra No se dejen castrar
ideologically castrated they want you weak they
ideológicamente los quieren débiles los
want you submissive they want you depressed they
quieren sumisos los quieren deprimidos
want you tamed they need to recover
los quieren domados necesitan recuperar
their masculinity they need to recover their
su masculinidad necesitan recuperar su
strength I don't even understand what
fuerza es que ni siquiera entiendo para
this is for I don't know if it's for I don't know if it is I don't know
esto no sé si es para no sé si es no sé
if this is a drink or something like that to
si esto es una bebida o algo así para
promote it let's see The truth is that I
promocionarlo a ver Es que la verdad me
thought it was very good gentlemen very good very
parecido muy buenas señores muy buenas
good I want to tell you all that
muy buenas quiero deciros a todos que
you have been wondering that
los que os habéis estado preguntando que
if everything that has happened these days and
si todo lo que ha ocurrido estos días y
so on has been a setup to make this
demás ha sido un montaje para hacer este
launch I want to tell you that yes I want to
lanzamiento quiero deciros que sí quiero
say one thing that neither my
decir una cosa que ni mi equipo de
marketing team nor I suspected under
marketing ni yo sospechábamos bajo
any circumstances that we were going to have
ningún concepto que íbamos a tener esta
such a big heavy reaction and that's why I
reacción tan heavy tan grande y por eso
want to apologize to all of you who have been
quiero pediros disculpas a todos los que
worried about what has happened
se han preocupado por lo que ha ocurrido
these days but if there is something that has
estos días pero si hay algo que ha
been clear and current is that we have
quedado claro y vigente es que tenemos
one of the most solid and
una de las comunidades más sólidas y
strong communities we have had the support of great
fuertes hemos tenido el apoyo de grandes
personalities Eh This shows that  I'm not
personalidades Eh Esto demuestra que no
alone this shows that we are not
estoy solo esto demuestra que no estamos
alone I will never trivialize the attacks
solos Jamás voy a banalizar los ataques
that the far left can commit
que pueden llegar a cometer la extrema
I mean with what has
izquierda quiero decir que con lo que ha
happened
ocurrido
with or rather they have faked or rather apparently
con o sea han fingido o sea por lo visto
these days they have also faked some
estos días han fingido también algún
kind of attack or something I don't know what it is about I do
tipo de ataque o algo no sé de qué trata
n't know if anyone can tell me in the
no sé si alguien me sabe decir en el
chat okay but or rather in the end what the
chat vale pero o sea al final qué [__]
[ __ ] is this I
[__] es esta
mean you would buy this drink after
O sea tú comprarías esta bebida después
seeing this but it's that there is nothing
de ver esto pero es que no hay nada que
I want less and and and it would be the last
me apetezca menos y y y sería la última
idea I had in my head
idea que tuviera yo en la en la cabeza
no what what the [ __ ] rash wasn't this
no qué qué mam rachada no ha sido esto
no now when should they come up
no ahora cuándo deberían darle venir por
behind him and hit him with the final bottle
detrás y pegarle el botellazo definitivo
no Javi you lack manhood Go [ __ ] yourself
no Javi te falta hombría Vete a la
Well also a little yes Factor
[__] Bueno también un poco sí Factor
we were very harsh with the sandwich But what the
fuimos muy duros con bocadillo Pero qué
[ __ ] happened he faked an attack on
[__] es lo que pasó fingió un ataque a
his car Ah It's true I
su coche Ah Es verdad lo
saw it in fact delox was one of the first
vi de hecho delox fue de los primeros
delox was one of the first to share it
delox fue de los primeros en compartirlo
How good delo Always deceiving
Qué bueno delo Siempre engañando a la
people Eh How strange no How strange let's
gente Eh Qué raro no Qué raro a
see how strange no delos helping a
ver qué raro no delos ayudando a un
hoax crazy guy has been found  with a little
engaño tío loco se ha encontrado con un
drawing about Dallas and what and what and he
dibujito que sobre Dallas y lo y lo y lo
shares it, dude, it's fatal, I mean, delo
comparte tío está fatal o sea delo
criticizing my law is weird eh I
criticando lo de mi ley está raro eh
also tell you, I don't understand much about that
También te digo no entiendo mucho de esa
thing, I should
movida tendría que
see it, he removed it, he already removed it or
verlo lo ha quitado ya lo ha quitado o
what, delos It doesn't fail but he removed it or what I mean, he
qué delos No falla pero lo ha quitado o
put something and then removed it, it
qué O sea puso algo y luego lo quitó es
seems to me I've seen it but I don't know
que me suena haberlo visto pero no sé en
where, it
dónde
seems to me I've seen the car attack, the
me suena haber visto lo del coche el
car attack, but no, I don't remember
ataque del coche pero no no me acuerdo
where I saw it, I don't know if it would come out or if
dónde lo he visto no sé si me saldría o
someone
alguien lo
challenged him, he removed it, no, or it must have been
retara lo ha quitado no o habrá sido en
somewhere else. How
otra parte Qué
strange he shared it on Instagram Javi Ah
raro lo compartió en instagram Javi Ah
well then it's not there anymore, no, but you see,
pues entonces ya no está no pero ya ves
not about deceiving them, no How
no del los engañando no Qué
strange we were very hard on you, forgive us,
raro fuimos muy duros contigo perdonanos
yao Cabrera
yao Cabrera
Well, look, speaking of yao Cabrera, the
Pues mira hablando de yao Cabrera la
truth is that I have to
verdad es que tengo que
show you something, I'm not going to see it on
mostraros una cosa no lo voy a ver en el
incai's Twitter, I think he
Twitter de incai que creo que é lo
shared it, talking about yao Cabrera,
compartió hablando de yao Cabrera
we have the arrest, no, yao Cabrera
tenemos la detención no yao Cabrera
is finally arrested after a year
finalmente es detenido después de un año
hiding from the law, I mean, look at you  how
escondiéndose de la ley o sea fíjate tú
long ago I didn't even remember
la de tiempo que hace Ya ni me acordaba
this guy no how long ago
de este pavo no la de tiempo que hace
this guy was convicted Ah It's true we have to
que este tío fue condenado Ah Es verdad
put the curb we have to put
hay que poner el bordillo hay que poner
the curb we're going to talk about Yao
el bordillo que vamos a hablar de yao
Cabrera let's see Yao let's see Yao he's the one
Cabrera a ver yao a ver yao él es él el
who hits the security guard and
que le pega al guarda de seguridad y es
he's the one who falls to the ground but Yao you
él el que se cae al suelo pero yao es
're a guard doll Pega that one just like
que eres un muñeco de guarda de Pega esa
you hit it Look I mean he's the one who
que tal y como la has pegado Mira o sea
hits the
va él es él el que le pega al guarda de
security guard and he's the one who falls to the ground
seguridad y es él el que se cae al suelo
but Yao you're a
pero yao es que eres un muñeco de
plasticine doll and the big guy comes this way
plastilina y el grandote viene por aquí
and he's going to put it in the other one but damn what a chew
y le le va a meter al otro pero [__]
my God look look at the
vaya mascada madre mía mira mira el
Big One How he deals out No look at the Big One
Grande Cómo reparte No mira el Grande
How he deals out here getting out of
Cómo va repartiendo aquí quitándose en
the way you don't hit like a girl Yao I [ __ ]
medio no pegas como una niña yao me cago
on everything let's see the video
en todo vamos a ver vdeo
well but what the [ __ ] are you doing
bien pero qué [__] estás haciendo
fighting with him or are you inviting him to
pelearte con él o lo estás invitando a
dance with you a Sevilla
que baile contigo una Sevilla
a
una
cor moment this moment is incredible not
cor momento este momento es increíble no
this moment
este momento
[Laughter]
[Risas]
it's how much your money has changed Javi
es cómo te ha cambiado la pasta Javi
you're more handsome No man We are  I'm the same damn I
estás más guapo No hombre Estamos igual
'm the same I'm the same let's
estoy igual [__] estoy igual estoy igual
see look at myself No man I'm older
a ver mirarme No hombre estoy más viejo
now I'm not older Yes I am older
ahora no estoy más viejo Sí estoy más
really Well I don't know if he's
viejo en verdad Bueno no sé si es más
older but maybe fatter Yes
viejo pero a lo mejor más gordito Sí
surely yes I have to lose weight to
seguramente sí tengo que adelgazar hasta
this point I think eh the funniest part of the
este punto yo creo eh más divertido del
video And we see how Yao comes
vídeo Y es que vemos como yao viene por
this way he doesn't make way he makes way
aquí no se abre camino se abre camino
here I mean he makes way I don't know if they are
aquí o sea se abre camino no sé si son
friends of them that are separating him
amigos de ellos que lo están separando
but here no they are not friends because he's the one that
pero aquí no no son amigos de porque es
slaps him look look at this
el que le mete la colleja mira mira esta
pose Look at this pose here divine and does
pose Mira esta pose aquí divina y hace
po catch yao come on Eat Eat a
po pilla yao venga Cómete Cómete un
little the curb Yao come here take it Tom
poquito el bordillo yao ven toma Tom
is hungry here Eat the curb a
tiene hambre toma Cómete el bordillo un
little let's see it with sound let's
poquito vamos a verlo con sonido vamos a
see it with sound it's very
verlo con sonido que es muy
funny the curb nothing happens
divertido el bordillo no pasa nada no
nothing happens everyone Have breakfast
pasa nada todo el mundo Desayuna
curb from time to time nothing This is what
bordillo de vez en cuando nada Esto es
happened today I think it's very
lo que ha pasado hoy Yo creo que es muy
funny for some is that the
divertido para alguno es que el vídeo
curb video is legendary eh I mean it's a
del bordillo es mítico eh o sea es un
legendary video from the Channel eh Well then
vídeo mítico del Canal eh Bueno pues
this guy is already in [ __ ] jail  Yeah, I mean,
este pavo ya la [__] cárcel ya o sea
but I think they're going to put him in
pero creo que lo van a meter en la
jail for the lesser of the crimes he's
cárcel por el menor de los delitos que
committed, no. I mean, I really didn't
ha cometido no O sea realmente no
fully understand the crime as such, he
terminé de entender el delito como tal
says about a year ago he was
dice hace más o menos un año ya fue
sentenced to 4 years in prison and since
condenado a 4 años de prisión y desde
then the law couldn't find the
entonces la ley no podía dar con el
whereabouts of the youtuber I also don't know if they would
paradero del youtuber Tampoco sé si lo
look for him much because normally
buscarían mucho pues normalmente la
people believe that when they sentence you to
gente se cree que cuando te condenan a
jail the police immediately goes
cárcel inmediatamente la policía va a
to your house and you go no Javi you are
buscarte a tu casa y vas no Javi estás
more handsome
más guapo corazón
red heart Yes man Yes really yes really
rojo Sí hombre Sí en verdad sí en verdad
yes let's see he was too thin there and
sí a ver estaba demasiado Delgado ahí y
too pale if I'm not mistaken,
demasiado pálido si no me equivoco
surely let's see the
seguramente a ver la
date December 17th he was here
fecha diciembre 17 estaba aquí
surely here he is already
seguramente ya aquí está
I was already starting to get sick and
yo estaba ya empezando a caer malo y
stuff like that You know, I spent a
esas cosas Sabes mucho me pegué una
while like falling really bad I fell
temporada como cayendo mucho malo caía
sick I don't know what
enfermo no sé qué
and and when I finally got the big outbreak it was
y y cuando ya me dio el brote gordo fue
at the beginning of 2018 you know and we already
al principio de 2018 sabes y ya
discovered that he had crom but
descubrimos que tenía crom pero
well
bueno
Ah, the thing is that this one hasn't filed the crime
Ah es que este no ha puesto el delito
remember that apart from paying with 4
recordemos que aparte de pagar con 4
years in prison he must pay
años de prisión debe pagar una
financial compensation to the victim in
compensación económica a la víctima con
the amount of 6 million pesos How much is
el monto de 6 millones de peso Cuánto es
that  Euro someone tells me in the
eso Euro me dice alguien por el
chat reduction to servitude
chat reducción a la servidumbre
em was reported in 2020 for
em fue denunciado en 2020 por
labor exploitation Okay and they talk about evading
laboral Vale y hablan de eludir la
justice but of course that's what I'm
justicia pero claro es que es lo que te
telling you I mean I don't know to what extent
digo o sea no sé hasta qué punto
eh I don't know how it is there but I
eh No sé cómo será allí pero yo tengo
understand that they put you in jail they
entendido que a ti te a ti te meten te
sentence you to jail not that you have to
condenan a cárcel no de que tengas que
enter and they summon you so that you go
entrar y a ti te citan para que tú vayas
to
a la
prison first time I hear you laugh
prisión primera vez que te escucho reíte
like that Ah well you've been here for a short time here
así Ah puces llevas poco tiempo aquí
here we laugh a lot
aquí aquí nos reímos mucho
eh
eh
em 600 Ah
em 600 Ah
18000 euros Well let's see if you
18000 euros Bueno a ver si os
[Music]
[Música]
in which if you don't show up at the
en las que si tú no te presentas en la
prison okay And you don't and you don't
prisión vale Y no te y no te
show up you don't enter voluntarily
presentas no ingresas tú voluntariamente
there are times when justice is not going
hay veces que la justicia no es que vay
to look for you or they are
a buscarte ni estén
combing the neighborhoods to
peinando los barrios para
find you when they catch you because they stop you
encontrarte cuando te pillen porque te
jumping the traffic light because you
paren saltado t semáforo porque te
get on a plane something you already They'll
montes en un avión alguna cosa ya te Ya
catch you do you understand but that's it No, well
te trincar me entiendes pero es eso No
now for whatever it is surely
pues ahora por lo que sea seguramente
Someone
alguien le
must have called the
habrá había pegado un toque a a la
police to tell them that Marcos
policía para para decirle que Marcos
Cabrera Rodriguez alias jao Cabrera
Cabrera Rodríguez alias jao Cabrera que
was wherever he was, okay, and they already have, and they already
estaba donde estuviera vale Y ya la han
caught her, eh, and they already caught her,
y ya la han cogido eh Y ya la han cogido
but that's what I'm telling you, I mean, with all the
pero es lo que te digo o sea con la de
things this
cosas que ha hecho este
guy has done, he's going to spend time in prison for, I don't even know
pavo va a pagar prisión a los no sé ni
how many
Cuántos
years he's worth. I don't even know how many years, almost
años vale No sé ni Cuántos años casi
6000, worth. That's definitive, I don't even know
6000 vale Esa sí es definitiva no sé ni
how many years it's been since
Cuántos años hace ya de las movidas de
this guy's actions and he's going to spend time in prison for the
este pavo y va a pagar prisión ahora por
least of these crimes. I mean, not to downplay its
el delito menos O sea no por quitarle
seriousness, eh, but of the things he's
gravedad eh pero de las cosas que ha
done, maybe it's the least serious,
hecho capaz y es lo menos grave
no, but oh well, one Uruguayan, at least missing, gbel
no pero bueno un uruguayo menos falta
joke, gbel joke joke, gbel, man, I know
gbel broma gbel broma broma gbel ches sé
the title of the video is a little weird,
que el título del vídeo es un poco raro
but it's real, okay, I'm wearing a
pero es realidad vale estoy con una
fox cap, they're the new caps he
gorra de zorro son las nuevas gorras que
's making, man, I almost always
está haciendo [__] tío casi siempre se
forget, eh, We didn't mention it, but the
me olvida eh No lo mencionamos pero lo
fox thing is, the store
de zorro la tienda
has it here, Fran fenx
la tiene aquí puesta Fran fenx
Club, damn, I always forget and
Club [__] es que siempre se me olvida y
in fact, I can't forget
además de hecho no se me puede olvidar
that I wanted to put it  me in the in the
que lo quería poner yo en el en el
rewind at the end the credits and and bu is
rewind al final los créditos y y bu es
that we have to fix the credits
que los créditos los tenemos que
completely the credits
arreglar por completo los créditos
because a lot of youtubers are missing that do
porque faltan un montón de youtubers que
collaborate okay
sí colaboran vale
e but here you can buy the t-shirts
e pero aquí podéis comprar las camisetas
and everything that you often ask us
y demás que muchas veces nos preguntáis
not because of the t-shirts and everything
no por el tema de las camisetas y demás
and and and they have good quality
y y y tienen buena calidad
eh I have to I have to order some
eh tengo que tengo que pedirme unas
black sweatshirts Well one of each I'm going to
sudaderas negra Bueno una de cada me voy
order the truth is one of
a pedir la verdad una de
each but yes yes I like these the
cada pero sí sí a mí me gustan estas la
typical ones okay these no these I don't
las típicas vale estas no estas no me
like these that much I want the typical ones these these I'm
gustan tanto Yo quiero las típicas estas
going to
estas las voy a
order what else What else What else
pedir qué más
What else do we have around here
Qué más Qué más Qué más tenemos por aquí
Fenex Club okay over there you have it over
fenex Club vale por ahí lo tenéis por
there you have it you can pay with PayPal
ahí lo tenéis podéis pagar con PayPal
with Google Pay it's from Zorro eh the
con Google Pay es de zorro eh la
Zorro company okay you already know
empresa zorro vale que ya sabéis está
the cap is nice eh Hey about the cap the
guapa la gorra eh Oye por la gorra lo
same thing I'll catch
mismo también me Pillo
eh man you had to do a
eh tío tenías que hacer un
raffle do you want me to do talking about
sorteo queréis que haga hablando de la
Fran's cap Look WhatsApp we've been
gorra de Fran Mira WhatsApp
watching it
lo hemos estado viendo
Karime we've been watching it you
Karime lo hemos estado viendo
want me to catch me to get a
que queréis que me pille que me pille un
pack and we'll raffle  this
pack y sorteamos esta
thing Go to the website that says in
movida Vais a ahí al Website que pone en
the description of the video about the fenx
la descripción del vídeo lo del fenx
club and that's it, what
club y ya está qué ha pasado lo que ha
happened is that they've filed a criminal complaint against me,
pasado es que me han puesto una querella
three criminal complaints, eh, I
criminal tres querellas criminales eh os
'm going to explain it to you as soon as I get there, now
lo voy a explicar en cuanto llegue ahora
the sanctuary that this here
el santuario que esto aquí de
here
aquí
Capi is the as soon as I get to the sanctuary
Capi es el en cuanto llegue al santuario
I'm going to sit in the office and I'll
me voy a sentar en la offi y os lo
explain it to you, they've filed three criminal complaints against me,
explico me han puesto tres querellas
in one they're asking for jail, they're asking for
criminales en una piden cárcel piden
deportation, they're asking for money and I'm going to explain
deportación piden dinero y voy exp
clearly what it is and above all the
claramente lo que es y sobre todo los
collateral damage that it carries with it, it's
daños colaterales que lleva encima es
a [ __ ] and I'm going to explain to you why
una putada y os voy a explicar por qué
three complaints why I even got a
tres querellas por qué me ha llegado
complaint So nothing Look at what a
querella Así que nada Mirad qué puesta
beautiful sunset and right after seeing this
bonita y justo después de ver esta
sunset from the sanctuary [ __ ]
puesta de sol desde el santuario [__]
man, these sunsets and all that, it's not that we do
tío que estas puestas de sol y demás no
n't see them here, well, they're
es que aquí no las vemos pues son
different man, let's watch the video guys, let's watch the
diferentes tío vamos al vídeo chavales
video, how different, man. Okay,
vamos al vídeo qué diferente tío Bueno
guys, I'm already in the office, what you
chavales ya estoy en la ofi esto que
see here, this is the criminal complaint that they've
veis aquí esto es la criminal que me han
filed against me, like this, they start Fran like this  They start
puesto así empiezan Fran así empiezan
with three complaints well it starts off slow
con tres querellas bueno empieza flojito
a bunch of papers it has the stamp the
un montón de papeles tiene con el sello
whole story I don't want to show it
toda la historia no lo quiero enseñar
because it's legal to show all those
porque no Es legal enseñar todos esos
official stamps but
sellos oficiales pero me ha llegado hace
a couple of days ago I received a criminal complaint
un par de días una querella criminal
as I told you at the beginning of the video
como os he dicho al principio del vídeo
What is a criminal complaint well it's
Qué es una querella criminal pues es
something that someone files on you because they want you to
algo que alguien te pone porque quiere
go to jail or if you're a
que vayas a la cárcel o si eres un
foreigner they want you deported in
extranjero quiere que te deporten en
this country it's
este país
not three complaints in one and all this
no son tres quellas en una y todo esto
sorry you're vaping grandpa no
perdonar estás vapeando abuelo no
Giorgio I was doing cocaine all
Giorgio me estaba metiendo cocaína todo
this started to take shape on
esto se empezó a fraguar el día 13 de
November 13th so my suspicions
noviembre con lo cual mis sospechas
when immigration came these guys came the
cuando vino inmigración vinieron los de
police the others my
estos los policías los otros mis
suspicions weren't unfounded and although I
sospechas no eran infundadas Y aunque
officially said well don't go and cause
dije oficialmente que bueno no vayáis a
[ __ ] don't say anything because no one
meter [__] no digáis nada porque no se
knows who it's from I already had a sneak peek at who it was
sabe de quién es Yo ya me olía de quién
even the animal police
venía incluso la policía animal me
warned me and
advirtió y me
said This is going to happen I didn't think they
dijo Esto va a pasar Yo tampoco pensé
were going to go that far but well they
que fueran a ir tan allá pero bueno me
filed a criminal complaint against me three in
han puesto una querella criminal tres en
one the cu Ah well that's better than
una las cu Ah bueno es mejor eso que
vaar Javi  in fact they are to destroy me
vaar Javi facto son para destruirme de
okay this is a complaint that has been
acuerdo esto es una querella que se haya
filed to gain something or to clear a
puesto para ganar algo o para limpiar un
name as they say or it has not been to
nombre como dicen o para no ha sido para
destroy me destroy me destroy the
destruirme destruirme a mí destruir el
sanctuary and as collateral damage
santuario y como daño colateral
to harming zorro I'm going to explain to you
a hacerle daño a zorro os voy a explicar
slowly and without much problem and without
despacito y sin mucho problema y sin
much history how this works well
mucha historia Cómo funciona esto bien
here there are three complaints the first is uh
aquí hay tres denuncias la primera es eh
For as a kind of right to honor
Por como una especie de derecho al honor
that is not the right to honor is
que no es derecho al honor está
reporting that because of me and for having
denunciando que por mi culpa y por haber
made a campaign against her her image
hecho una campaña contra ella su imagen
has
se ha
deteriorated I have destroyed her
deteriorado he destrozado su imagen
public image let's see the issue of the right to
pública a ver el tema del derecho al
honor
honor
and both here in Spain and in almost
e tanto aquí en España como en casi
all countries
todos los países
the right to honor is not that or
em el derecho al honor no es que o sea
the right to honor is that you have
el derecho al honor es que tú hayas
damaged the image of that person or the
dañado la imagen de esa persona o sea el
right to honor in the end it is something very
derecho al honor al final es algo muy
subjective when it comes to the Judge in whom it
subjetivo a la hora del Juez en el que
falls uh because we have seen cases in which
caiga eh porque hemos visto casos en los
suddenly an atrocity is not condemned
que de repente una barbaridad no se
and a stupid thing is condemned okay uh of
condena y una tontería s se condena vale
course when we talk about condemning it does not
eh claro cuando hablamos de condenar no
mean that condemning and it is
significa que condenar e no es todo
not all black or white okay for example in me
blanco o negro vale por ejemplo a mí en
the sentence that they gave me Of course they
la condena esta que me pusieron Claro
sentenced because they sentenced me to delete
condenaban porque condenaban a borrar
the videos you know what I mean, they weren't going to
los vídeos me entiendes no me iban a
make me pay 80,000 like the guy asked
hacer pagar 80,000 como pedía el colega
no but it was Look yes remove the
no sino que era Mira sí quitar los
videos Because these videos are more
vídeos Porque estos vídeos son más
disproportionate I don't know what I don't know how much they're
desproporcionados no sé qué no sé cuánto
worth they're there they damage the image of this
vale están ahí dañan la imagen de esta
person but you also have to keep in
persona pero también tené que tener en
mind that the right to honor is
cuenta que el derecho al honor muchas
often taken as e Of
veces la gente se lo toma como
course what [ __ ] It's very
e Claro que que [__] Es que es muy
relative dude it's very relative because that's what it has to
relativo tío es muy relativo porque es
be that it damages your image that it
que tiene que ser que dañe tu imagen que
damages your reputation
dañe tu reputación
that it changes the perception Maybe of the of what
que cambie la percepción A lo mejor de
people have of the
la de la de lo que la gente tiene de la
image that people have of you not the one
imagen que tiene la gente sobre ti no la
you would like to have I don't know the truth it
que tú quisieras tener no sé la verdad
's a problem eh But well here in
es un rollo eso eh Pero bueno aquí en
Asia apparently the
Asia por lo visto Están muy penado el
issue of the right to honor is very punishable it's a thing
tema del derecho al honor es una cosa
there in Asia as such in general not only
allí en Asia como tal en general no solo
in Thailand that they take very
en Tailandia que que se toman muy en
seriously and that he is not able to get the
serio y que no es capaz de conseguir los
jobs he wants or something like that no that
trabajos que quiere o una cosa así no
later I will also tell you
que después también te digo
about Fran, about Yuji, what Fran talked about
lo de Fran lo de yuji lo que Fran habló
this is talked about in  It was discussed in Spain, that
esto se habla en se habló en España o
is, in Thailand. This was not discussed that
sea en Tailandia Esto no se habló que
Yui is looking for sponsorship promotions in Thailand, that is, in Spain, no,
yui en Tailandia o sea en España no
because in any case, Yuji's bad image is
porque en todo caso la imagen mala de
in Spain,
yuji la tiene en España
eh, I don't know if. Well, I know what's going to be
eh yo no sé si Bueno yo sé lo que se va
fought, it's going to have to be fought, but
a pelear va a haber que pelearlo pero
that is one of the complaints that has
eso es una de las denuncias que ha
lost credibility
perdido credibilidad
and image here in Thailand
e Imagen aquí en Tailandia
because, well, I don't know the truth, okay, because
porque pues no sé la verdad vale porque
here, nothing is said about all of that,
aquí de aquí no se habla nada de todo
nor has it been discussed. Well, that is the
eso ni se ha hablado bueno esa es la
first. The second is to say that I
primera la segunda es para decir que yo
did some live broadcasts on Kiik in which I
hice unos directos de kiik en los cuales
asked for money to come illegally
pedí dinero para que viniera ilegalmente
to Thailand because I don't have a
a Tailandia porque no tengo un permiso
specific work permit for Kik, and also
de trabajo específico para kik y también
that I am making YouTube videos in
que estoy haciendo vídeos de YouTube en
which I am abusing
los cuales estoy abusando de los
animals, eh. And I don't have a
animales eh Y no tengo un permiso
specific work permit for YouTube, okay,
específico de trabajo para YouTube vale
specific, okay.
específico de acuerdo
Ah, that would be the second
Ah esa sería la segunda delito
tax offense. eh, third, that I have
fiscal eh tercera que tengo animales
protected animals inside the sanctuary in poor
protegidos dentro del santuario en mal
condition, that I am using them to
estado que los estoy utilizando para
make the videos, and that I have set up
hacer los vídeos y que me he montado
a place here in which I have, eh,
aquí un zo en el cual tengo eh animales
illegal animals, okay.
ilegales de acuerdo
Ah, it is the authorities who call
Ah son las autoridades las que lo llaman
him to collect the
a él para que recojas los
animals.  Those are the three complaints that
animales Esas son las tres denuncias que
criminals have filed against me, it costs a fortune
me ha puesto criminales cuesta una pasta
here to do that, eh,
aquí hacer eso eh
eh And what does this mean? Does this
eh Y esto qué quiere decir esto quiere
mean that I can go to jail? They can
decir que puedo ir a la cárcel Me pueden
deport me and also, they can give me a
deportar y aparte Me pueden poner una
big fine, you can win, you can
multa gorda se puede ganar se puede
win, I'll explain it to you, eh,
ganar yo os explico eh
I don't know, I mean, Fran was already telling me this a few
Yo es que no sé o sea yo esto ya me me
days ago. Eh, and I did
lo vino contando Fran hace días Eh e yo
n't know that he was going to upload a video so
no sabía que iba a subir el un vídeo tan
quickly, I mean, eh, he had been telling me this
rápido o sea eh él me lo venía contando
for days, at first, he had made a
hace días en principio él tenía una
decision which was basically to
decisión tomada que era básicamente pues
leave Thailand or something like that,
irse de Tailandia o algo por el estilo
okay, but finally, he surprised me
vale pero pero finalmente me sorprende
the other day when we were on the
el otro día cuando estábamos en el
live stream he said, no, no, hey, I'm going to
directo que me dice no no Oye lo voy a
fight it, eh, I don't know if you noticed at the
pelear eh No sé si os disteis cuenta al
end of the live stream, more or less when he
final del directo más o menos cuando
's making a sandwich, eh, he says,
está haciendose sándwich eh Me dice
well, I don't know what, of course, and he already told me
Bueno no sé qué claro y ya me dijo
last night that it was going to be a video, the whole time,
anoche como que iba a serc un vídeo todo
but I didn't know that he was going to
el ry ese pero no sabía que lo iba a
do it so
hacer tan
quickly. Two days ago, I spoke to a lawyer, he
rápido dos días hablé con con un abogado
wasn't a criminal lawyer and he said, how about you
no era penalista y me dijo qué tal no le
ask your friend Cruz?  I imagine that he
preguntarás a tuyupa Cruz Me imagino que
will have spoken with your husband to him, so in the
habrá hablado con tuyupa a él o sea al
end it is an issue for him, you understand, I
final es un tema de él me entiendes o
mean, I am here to help him in whatever is
sea yo estoy aquí para ayudarle en lo
in my power, which is almost
que esté en mi mano que es pues casi
nothing, really, more than giving him moral
nada la verdad más que darle apoyo moral
and emotional support and such, you understand. I
y emocional y y tal me entiendes O sea
mean, here I can't do anything, it's not
que aquí no puedo hacer yo nada no es
like we can do
como que podamos hacer
a 24-hour live broadcast. You understand. The way
un directo de 24 horas Me entiendes Como
he saw it, I could leave
lo veía él ya me podía ir de Tailandia
Thailand before starting the process because they were going to charge me because I was going to end up in jail. What they are basically asking for is to beat me up, okay? And the truth is that I thought, I say, well, if you leave Thailand, you start
Bueno si te vas Tailandia te empiezas en
somewhere else, but I have set up this
otro sitio pero yo he montado este
sanctuary, personally, what I
santuario yo personalmente lo que le
told him was to leave Thailand, okay, they can
dije fue que se fuera de Tailandia vale
sell the land,
que las tierras las vendan las vendan
these people can sell it when they can, you know, I mean, in the
esta gente cuando puedan sabes o sea al
end, that has an enormous economic value, they
final eso tiene un valor económico
are already theirs and the whole thing about the
enorme ya son suyas y todo el rollo del
son, no, they can sell it, they can sell everything, let him
hijo no que lo vendan que lo vendan todo
find a way to make the
que busque la manera de hacer los
animals but the thing is, the thing is,
animales pero es que a ver el tema es
the thing is that with that option, the
que el tema es que esa opción los
animals are abandoned, of course, but let's
animales los dej abandonados claro pero
see if you  They're going to put you in
a ver si te van a meter en la
jail, of course, the point is that, but
cárcel claro el tema es que eso pero
of course, if they're going to put you in
claro es que si te van a meter en la
jail, you'll have to leave. No, I mean, if they're going to deport you.
cárcel tendrás que irte no O sea si te
Anyway, no. Either they're going to
van a deportar Igualmente no O te van a
put you in jail or they're going to deport you.
meter la cárcel o te van a deportar
Anyway, you know what the [ __ ] you do with the
Igualmente sabes qué [__] haces con los
animals, what the [ __ ] do you do with all the
animales qué [__] haces con todas las
ostriches,
avestruces
you know, it's a mess, that's it, eh, but man, I
sabes es una movida eso eh pero hombre
understand that there will be an organization. I don't know what
entiendo que habrá un organismo No sé lo
the animals would do, the truth is, I don't
que harían los animales la verdad no sé
know what they would do, I don't know what they would do, but of course, what I
harían no sé lo que harían pero claro yo
told him was, look, Juan
lo que que le dije fue Mira Juan Luis
Luis Malpartida, I go almost every weekend to see Juan Luis
los fines de semana a ver a Juan Luis
Malpartida. Juan Luis Malpartida has his
malpartida Juan Luis malpartida tiene
shelter set up here in Seville. Okay, I go to see him
e el refugio suyo vale Yo voy a verlo
every weekend because you
todos los fines de semana porque ya
know what Leo is like. Okay, one
sabéis Cómo es Leo vale un día voy a
day I'm going to do a
haceros un un día voy a haceros un
report on you and he. Look, this was
reportaje d de ju le y é Mira Esto fue
the other day. Oh, look, two years ago. Okay,
el otro día Ah mira hace dos años Vale
so the other day he does the same thing. He has
pues el otro día él hace igual él tiene
an area where Los Lobos are and he goes
una zona donde está Los Lobos y él se va
there for a little while and takes his walk with
para allá un ratito se pega su paseo con
Los  Wolves in the end they are animals
Los Lobos sea al final son animales
just like FR But this does smell bad about
igual que FR Pero esto Sí huele feo por
what you experienced with Daniel Sancho do
punto lo que viviste de Daniel Sancho
you think justice is not so manipulative
crees cu la justicia no es tan manipu
poor Frank better to stay single Dante
pobre Frank mejor quedarse soltero Dante
not to me when Fran told me I
yo a mí no cuando me lo contó Fran yo lo
see him weak Well now he's going to keep
veo flojo Bueno ahora va a seguir
talking I see him weak the
hablando yo lo veo flojo la
truth is I don't know you're going to
verdad que no sé que te vas a meter la
jail for this let's see if I know that I do know
cárcel por esto a ver si sé que si sé
that the issue of honor can be very
que el tema del honor si puede ser muy
difficult in Spain and we would have to
[__] en España y tendríamos que
review maybe but of course what
revisar a lo mejor pero claro qué qué ha
Fran could have said that violates
podido decir Fran que vulnere el honor
Yuji's honor about the drugs if
de yuji lo de la droga si la ha contado
she told it or rather if Fran already responded because
ella o sea si Fran ya respondió porque
she told it Fran was lying to
ella lo contó Fran Estaba mintiendo por
protect her that I also imagine
protegerla que eso también me imagino
that he will use it in his defense no I mean
que lo utilizará en su defensa no O sea
but if I was I was lying on
pero si yo estaba yo estaba mintiendo en
all the in all the programs on the
todos los en todos los programas del
planet to defend her, I mean I said
planeta para defenderla o sea yo dije
that they were unjustly putting her in
que la estaban metiendo injustamente en
jail and the truth already came out Now the
la cárcel y ya salió la verdad Ahora la
truth It came out now because she told it
verdad Salió ahora porque ella lo contó
on a program before him I mean what
en un programa antes que é O sea qué es
can come out I don't
lo que puede salir No no
know  I hope he wins it, I don't know, honestly,
sé yo espero que lo gane no sé la verdad
I hope he
yo espero que lo
wins the issue, the issue of
gane el tema el tema de lo de la
regularity with, with making content,
regularidad con con con hacer contenido
I imagine that he will have it more than
me imagino que lo tendrá más que
solved with the time, the
solucionado con la de tiempo que la de
years that he has been making content, I mean,
años que lleva haciendo contenido o sea
how many years has Fran been making
cuántos años tiene Fran haciendo
content, he will have that more than not and
contenido lo tendrá eso ya más que no y
then what was the other thing? Oh, the thing about the
luego que era lo otro Ah lo de los
animals, well, it's as simple as
animales pues es tan sencillo como
visualizing that there is no animal abuse,
visualizar que no hay maltrato animal
no, I don't know, but well, I would have
no no sé pero bueno esto yo me hubiera
come to Spain, bought some
venido para España compro un
land, okay? And look, Juan Luis, in the end, he
terreno vale Y mira Juan Luis al final
has the same thing, it's the same, animals
tiene lo mismo sea es lo mismo animales
that for whatever reason they have tried to
que por lo que sean los han intentado
trick them, I don't know what. And he goes, he picks them up, I
trapichear No sé qué Y él los va los
mean, he picks them up
recoge o sea él lo recoge
and they are animals that are raised there with
y y son animales que se crían allí con
him, it's like a sanctuary, I mean, the truth is that what
él es como un santuario o sea en verdad
happens is that it has the part where
lo que pasa que tiene la parte en la que
you can visit, which is not the whole thing, it's
tú pues puedes visitar que no es toda es
a zoological part, let's not say no, which I
una parte zoológica no digamos no que me
imagine will be to finance himself. I have been
imagino que será para financiarse yo
living in Thailand for 27 years, I have
llevo 27 años viviendo en Tailandia no
never had any legal problems, I have not
he tenido nunca ningún problema legal no
had any problems of any
he tenido ningún problema de ningún un
kind in that sense and I have set up this
tipo en ese sentido y yo he montado este
sanctuary so that the animals that
santuario para que los animales que
were in  terrible conditions or
estaban en unas condiciones pésimas o
that they were going to have
que iban a tener unas condiciones
terrible living conditions can have a second
pésimas de vida puedan tener una segunda
chance And being animals I'm not going
oportunidad Y ser animales yo no me voy
to leave here until they kick me out or until they
a ir de aquí hasta que me echen o hasta
put me in jail and I can't
que me metan en la cárcel y no pueda
take care of them okay I know what they
cuidarlos de acuerdo sé que lo que
want is
quieren es
eh Well that I don't have any permit
Eh Pues eso que no tenga ningún permiso
that they take away from me Thank you sol what are you doing
que me quiten Gracias sol que haces
wake up well what are you doing wake up
despierta bueno que haces despierta
of course what are you doing here until now I didn't
claro qué haces aquí hasta ahora que no
expect you Thank you so much solaje is
te esperaba Muchísimas gracias solaje
always supporting us all the
siempre nos está apoyando todos los
content solaje both in the primary
contenidos solaje tanto en el principal
as in the secondary as in the
como en el secundario como en el
tertiary as in the quintary a kiss
terciario como en el quintario un beso
beautiful Thank you so much
guapísima Muchísimas gracias
sweetheart in everything and that they take the animals away from me
corazón en todo y que me saquen los
that is what they are looking for
animales eso es lo que están buscando
because they do harm in that way it is a
porque hacen daño de esa manera es una
very tricky complaint it is a complaint that I will
denuncia muy tricky es una denuncia que
now explain to you Why it is going to
ahora os explicaré Por qué se va a
turn against me and a lot
volver en contra y mucho
and and the YouTube issue the issue of such and such also does not
y y el tema de YouTube el tema de tal
realize that that money
tampoco se da cuenta de que ese dinero
was because because as I would define it a
era porque porque como yo le definira un
blackmail I mean
chantaje es decir
eh if I wanted him to put the land in the
eh si yo quería que pusiera la tierra
name of his children Ah It's true of course or I
nombre de sus hijos Ah Es verdad claro o
mean  if she earned the money, what the
sea si el dinero le ha ganado ella qué
[ __ ] is she doing, what the [ __ ] is she claiming from
[__] le van qué [__] le está reclamando
him because he worked without, without regulating,
a él porque ha trabajado sin sin regular
if the money has stayed with her or in the
si el dinero se ha quedado ella o a
name of her son's fox, eh, he had to
nombre de zorro de su hijo eh tenía que
pay her money, he had to buy back the
pagarle un dinero tenía que recomprar el
sanctuary, well, that will be fought, it will be fought
santuario bien eso se luchará se peleará
But those are the three complaints that he has
Pero eso son las tres querellas que ha
filed, I know that from Europe it looks
puesto sé que desde Europa se ve
stupid and absurd Yes, yes, I totally
estúpido y absurdo Sí sí yo totalmente
see it. Of course, I'm telling you, let's see, no, we
lo ve Claro ya te digo sea ver no no
're not there, eh, in California, it's 5:00,
estamos allí eh en California son las 5
6:15 in the afternoon,
las 6:15 o sea de la tarde
Solange. Well, a kiss for California,
solange Pues un beso para California
Javi, do you think that the
Javi crees que se puede solicitar al
government of Thailand can be asked for protection for Fran
gobierno de Tailandia protección a Fran
and the
y al
sanctuary? I have no idea,
santuario Es que no tengo ni idea eso ya
Fran will say that
lo irá diciendo Fran de alguna
somehow, it will come up here. Fran will
manera ya subirá por aquí Fran
surely come up someday
seguramente estos días subirá algún día
or we'll talk about it on
o lo hablaremos el
Sunday, we'll talk about it on Sunday,
domingo lo hablaremos el domingo
surely, but I don't know, of course, I
seguramente pero no sé es que claro yo
see it and it is what it is, what he says, it
lo veo y es lo que es lo que él dice a
seems stupid to me, but why?
mí me parece estúpido pero por qué
Because I live here, but it's that
Porque yo vivo aquí pero es que ya la la
justice in Asia. I mean, no, it can't be
justicia en Asia O sea no no se puede
compared. We've already seen it. I mean, it can't
comparar Ya lo hemos visto O sea no se
be compared, it can't be  compare or
puede comparar no se puede comparar o
rather what do I see here, well
sea yo aquí qué es lo que veo pues que
here what right to honor No what the
aquí que qué derecho al honor No qué
[ __ ] are things that she herself
pollas son cosas que ella misma
in the case that there was some insult in
en el caso que hubiera algún insulto en
any of Fran's live shows that right now I don't
alguno de los directos de Fran que ahora
remember well a
mismo de memoria lo desconozco pues una
fine no
multa no
and and the issue of regulating here for example
y y el tema de regular aquí por ejemplo
in Spain when you do something irregular
en España cuando tú haces algo irregular
in an imposed issue doing what you do
de tema impuesto haciendo lo que haces
asking you for money and maybe with
pedirte el dinero y a lo mejor con
interest with a little bit of interest
interese con un poquito de interese A lo
Maybe eh Because most of the time it
mejor eh Porque la mayoría de las veces
's an agreement so that you pay and out
es acuerdo para que tú pagues y fuera
[Music]
[Música]
eh you know I can't think of a way that
eh sabes que no se me ocurre la manera
here in Spain they would put you in
de que aquí en España te metieran en la
jail for something like that you
cárcel por algo así
know and it's not like even if they sentenced you
saes y ni es que ni aunque te condenaran
to prison they would sentence you to something so that you end up in
a prisión te condenarían a algo para que
jail you understand the
llegues a pisa la cárcel me entiendes el
issue is that here here in Thailand For
tema es que aquí aquí en Tailandia Por
example if they sentence him to prison he goes
ejemplo si le condenan a prisión él va
to prison for the moment you know the [ __ ]
de momento a la prisión sabes [__]
look at Yuji not with Yuji yes it's
fijaros con yuji no con yuji sí es
true that she yes it's true that she had
verdad que ella si es verdad que tenía
drugs yes it's true that she had that
droga si es verdad que tenía ese
problem but not drug trafficking
problema pero no un tráfico de droga
How was what they put her in no and  It
Cómo era lo que le metieron no y le
took him 6 years to get her acquitted in the end
costó 6 años sacarla absuelta al final
because of course it was his own consumption
porque claro era un consumo
[Music]
[Música]
So what I'm telling you, I don't know
Entonces entonces lo que te digo no sé
what can happen, the truth is, he's
qué puede pasar la verdad él él está
worried, he thinks that they can
preocupado él cree que que le pueden
put him in jail and then I'll have to
meter la cárcel y luego tendré que
fight it, you know, and America will also look
pelearlo sabes y América también se verá
stupid, absurd, but here the laws
estúpido absurdo pero aquí las leyes
work differently, the courts
funcionan de otra manera los juzgados
work differently, and here, if you
funcionan de otra manera y aquí como
have uh affinity and above all, a lot of
tengas eh afinidad y sobre todo mucho
money, things can work in
dinero puede llegar a funcionar de
some different way,
alguna manera diferente
okay, especially in a case that is
vale especialmente en un caso que no es
neither blood nor hard drugs nor
ni de sangre ni de drogas fuertes ni de
this nor that,
esto ni lo otro
what can happen to me? Well, there are sentences of
no qué me puede pasar pues Hay penas de
up to 5 years that they can put me in
hasta 5 años que me pueden meter de
jail, stipulated by the law, what are they
cárcel estipulado por la ley qué me
accusing me of? Well, all the crimes that I've
imputan Pues todos los delitos que os he
told you about, and what's the problem here? They
dicho y cuál es la putada aquí que ellos
don't think about collateral damage, in
no piensan en los daños colaterales de
no
ninguna
way, the owner of the land is a
manera el dueño de la tierra es
fox, if they condemn me for a crime, they
zorro si a mí me condenan por un delito
condemn the fox, he is the owner of the
condenan él es el dueño de la
land, he is the one who theoretically is
tierra él es el que teóricamente me está
letting me commit crimes here, according to his
dejando aquí cometer delitos según su
mother, of course, which makes him an accomplice to
madre claro con lo cual es cómplice de
a little
un
finger, which would
dedito con lo cual se abriría
automatically open the case  uh an instruction on
automáticamente eh una instrucción sobre
him also means that they haven't thought
él también es decir que no han pensado
about that or yes Why Because he is going to
en eso o sí Por qué Porque él va a ir a
testify too Surely Zape will
declarar también Seguramente zape se
come from Spain to testify And
venga desde España a declarar Y
surely his daughter who is really pissed off
seguramente su hija que tiene un cabreo
uh Also ends up
de la [__] eh También termine
testifying even though she is a minor why
declarando aunque sea menor por qué
because this is done to cause harm It will be
porque esto se hace para hacer daño Ya
explained in the trial
se explicará en el juicio
uh things
eh las cosas
but if theoretically it has damaged his image
pero si teóricamente ha dañado su imagen
what image in Spain in South America in
qué imagen en España en Sudamérica en
Russia in the United States which is where more
Rusia en Estados Unidos que es donde más
or less people see me Central America
o menos la gente me ve Centroamérica
North America where in Thailand in
Norteamérica dónde en Tailandia en
Thailand they don't even know the table to the
Tailandia no saben ni ni la mesa a la
half
media
uh that I committed a crime with the
eh que yo cometí delito con el tema de
kik issue and that I talked [ __ ] about her and
kik y que yo hablaba [__] de ella y
that I got money by talking bad
que conseguí dinero a base de hablar mal
about her No I didn't speak
de ella No yo no hablé mal de ella yo
badly about her I said what was happening and why we were asking for donations to pay her in fact all that money was for her Of course she is asking for damages for such Well well it has been proven that I have given her more than 250,000 in
está que yo le he dado más de 250,000 en
the last 2 years of
los últimos 2 años
course idiot me it doesn't make sense I
claro tonto yo es que no tiene sentido O
mean what money are you going to  ask clearly
sea si qué dinero Le vas a pedir claro
for example well this is criminal I don't
por ejemplo bueno Esto que es penal no
understand no but here in Spain a
entiendo no pero aquí en España una
civil a civil lawsuit is because
civil una demanda civil es porque
someone considers that another person
alguien considera que otra persona le
owes them money no for example the lawsuits
debe dinero no por ejemplo las demandas
are for right to honor you don't owe me
estas por derecho al honor no me debes
money for the damage that you have done to my
dinero por el daño que has hecho a mi
image earning money no
imagen ganando dinero no
[Music]
[Música]
eh what are you claiming no that based on
eh qué está reclamando no que en base a
what if the money from all these acts has been
qué si el dinero de todos estos actos se
taken by her or rather there is no
lo ha llevado ella o sea no hay un
profit that at Christmas talking to my
lucro que en Navidades hablando con mis
children I was bothering them so
hijos les estuve dando el [__] para
that they would be with their mother so that they would
que estuvieran con su madre para que
try to smooth out their laziness eh I
intentaran limar las perezas eh
got them to go to eat on
conseguí que fueran a comer el día de
Christmas Day to go to eat with her
Navidad a que fueran a comer con ella
after Christmas Eve the next day to
después de Nochebuena al día siguiente
go to eat with her a few
que fueran a comer con ella hace unos
days ago Zen wanted to be with his dog so and
días zen quería estar con su perro tal y
so I let him go with his mother tad I
cual le dejé que fuera con su madre tad
told him well Hey stay with your mother for
le dije pues Oye quédate con tu madre
a few days I told you a long time ago
unos días yo os lo dije hace tiempo
until I leave
hasta que no me vaya de
Thailand they won't rest what happens is
Tailandia no van a descansar lo que pasa
that this is going to turn against me I
es que esto se va a volver en contra Yo
could lose one of those three cases I will
puedo perder alguno de esos tres casos
surely lose some surely something will
seguramente pierda alguno seguramente
happen I know I know or maybe  the
algo pase lo sé lo sé o a lo mejor los
three of them and I'm done Well that's a year in
tres y termino Pues eso un año en la
jail or two or deported or whatever
cárcel o dos o dep portado o lo que sea
then it was to explain that to you
entonces era explicaros eso
eh what hurts me the most Is that zorro is
eh lo que más me duele Es que zorro se
going to get one because Obviously the
va a llevar una porque Obviamente el
lawyer has said let's see eh if she wanted you to
abogado ha dicho a ver eh si ella quería
make a contract for the
que hicieras un contrato de la del
site or I mean I had to sign
sitio o sea es que yo le tuve que firmar
a contract do you remember a rental so
un contrato os acordáis de alquiler para
that if something happened she wouldn't have
que si pasaba algo ella no tuviera
any charges or anything or anything How
ninguna imputación ni nada ni tal Qué
strong this eh I mean the reason why
fuerte esto eh o sea el motivo por el
she had
que ella tenía
the sanctuary was because of the issue that he
e el santuario era por el tema de que él
couldn't have it not in his name but eh
no podía tenerlo no a su nombre pero Eh
yes they had a rental contract in
sí que tenían un contrato de alquiler en
the last few years for Well I don't know if years
los últimos años por Bueno no sé si años
or months I think a year and a half maybe or
o meses creo que año y pico a lo mejor o
2 years because of the issue that there was a
2 años por el tema de que hubiera una
responsibility only on him for what
responsabilidad solo en él de lo que
was happening inside the sanctuary And
estaba pasando en dentro del santuario Y
so she to get her hands off
entonces ella para librarse de las manos
in case something happened inside the sanctuary
por si pasaba algo dentro del santuario
that was not her responsibility has
que no fuera responsabilidad suya ha
done the same thing now with her son this is
hecho lo mismo ahora con su hijo esto es
tremendous And that this is tremendous this
tremendo Y esa esto es tremendo esa
complaint that she feared they would put on
denuncia que ella temía que le pusieran
her for being the  owner of the
a ella por ser la propietaria de la
land she has put her
tierra la ha puesto ella
now the same one that she was
ahora la misma de la que ella tenía
afraid of being put on her when she was the
miedo que le pusieran cuando ella era la
owner of the land What does it mean that
dueña de la tierra Qué quiere decir que
here at the moment that the
aquí en el momento que esté la
investigation is later on, then zorro is going to
investigación más adelante pues zorro va
have a problem because he is the
a tener un problema porque él es el
owner of the land and he is with me
dueño de la tierra y él está conmigo
here He is here with me he is part of the
aquí Él está aquí conmigo es parte del
sanctuary
santuario
eh And that I will
eh Y
not pass so
eso eso ya no lo paso entonces que
you know that these are going to be hard months I was
sepáis que van a ser meses duros os
telling you the other day that you have to be
decía el otro día que hay que estar
happy every
feliz todos los
day hard months because on
días meses duros porque el día 6 de
March 6th I have to go to court they are going to
marzo yo tengo que ir al juzgado me van
read the charges to me and I am going to have
a leer las imputaciones y voy a tener
about TR months more or less with the lawyer
unos TR meses más o menos con el abogado
to answer all those charges
para contestar a todas esas imputaciones
and I tell you in the best of cases I
y ya os digo en el mejor de los casos me
get a little but something is going to come to me
cae un poco pero algo me va a caer
because it is very well prepared they have
porque está muy bien preparada han
had many months eh to prepare
tenido muchos meses eh para preparar
this
esto
eh remember that here The police already came
eh acordaros que aquí Ya vino la policía
Once immigration came they came so and so they have been for
Una vez vino inmigración vino
many months they have been
tal llevan muchos meses llevan desde
preparing it since November, since October and
noviembre desde octubre preparándolo y
since November when the complaint was filed
desde noviembre que se puso la querella
and now after the
y ahora pues ya después de las
investigations that the police
investigaciones que ha hecho la policía
immigration has done all that  had
inmigración todo aquello que había
happened Well now a couple of days ago
pasado Pues ahora ya hace un par de días
I received that notification with
me ha llegado esa notificación con toda
the entire complaint and on March 6th the judge
la querella y el día 6 de marzo el juez
will read me the charges and I will have Well
me leerá las imputaciones y tendré Pues
that three months or two months or a month to be
eso tres meses o dos meses o un mes para
able to respond and
poder contestar y
defend myself it could be the end of
defenderme puede ser el final de
sanctuary yes be the end of a time
santuario sí ser el final de un tiempo
of freedom for me also it could
en libertad mío también puede que me
cost me money it is going to cost me a lot of
cueste dinero me va a costar mucho
money this
dinero esto
uh it could collaterally affect my
eh puede que afecte colateralmente a mis
children totally because I am the
hijos totalmente porque yo soy el
foundation of the family I am the one who
fundamento de la familia Yo soy el que
supports the family and at the end of the day
mantiene la familia y al final del día
uh all of this is going to harm many
eh todo esto va a dañar a bastante
more beings both human and non-human
más seres tanto humanos como no humanos
than they thought it seems to me a
de lo que se pensaban me parece una
truly ruined
auténtica ruine
mu ru something very dirty and something that now I
mu ru algo muy sucio y algo que ahora sí
will never forgive I am not
que no voy a perdonar jamás yo no estoy
at war I am not an enemy of anyone
en guerra yo no soy enemigo de nadie
but when you already do things that
pero cuando tú ya haces cosas que
affect your children directly
afectan a tus hijos directamente
judicially
judicialmente
and in their lives already on a
y en su vida ya a
very personal level
nivel muy personal
eh I am very sorry that way it cannot
eh Lo siento mucho por ahí no se puede
happen I could leave the country
pasar me podía ir del país
and get rid of everything yes I will leave the
y librarme de todo sí voy a dejar a los
animals here alone no they will take me out
animales aquí solos no a mí me sacarán
of here to jail or  They'll take me to
de aquí para la cárcel o me sacarán para
the
el
airport But I'm not
aeropuerto Pero yo a los animales no los
going to leave the animals here alone because it's my
voy a dejar aquí solos porque es mi
responsibility to be here until the
responsabilidad el estar aquí hasta el
day they arrest me, take me to
día que me detengan me lleven a la
jail or until the day they take me out of the
cárcel o hasta el día que me saquen del
country and deport me and they don't let me back
país y me deporten y no me dejen volver
in 20 years, that's what they're looking for, that's
en 20 años eso es lo que buscan eso es
what they'll possibly
lo que posiblemente
get but I believe that in life what
consigan pero yo creo que en la vida lo
is fair is fair and whoever does
que es justo es justo y el que hace las
things with malice sooner or later will
cosas con maldad tarde o temprano pues
meet the shape of their
pues se encontrará con la orma de su
shoe. Did you see that laser supports
zapato de Ya viste que láser apoya la ex
Franc's ex? Yes, we've been seeing it before,
de franc sí lo hemos estado viendo antes
it's what is expected, agreement, it's what was
es lo que se espera acuerdo es lo que se
expected, eh, I could ask for damages, I
esperaba eh yo podría pedir daños y
could ask for many things but
perjuicios podía pedir muchas cosas pero
the funny thing is that that person that
lo curioso es que esa persona
I took to more than 15
que que yo la llevé a más de 15 centros
rehabilitation centers, hospitals,
de rehabilitación hospitales
treatments, that for 6 years and something
tratamientos que durante 6 años y algo
in jail, what F I took care of, that she
en la cárcel qué F cuidé de que
was in the best part of jail,
estuviera en la mejor parte de la cárcel
paying and spending
pagando y gastando
money. That person that I went to every
dinero Esa persona que yo iba todas las
[ __ ] early morning to bring her food. That
[__] madrugadas a llevarle comida Esa
person that I took care of, the family and we didn't
persona que yo cuidé la familia y no nos
move from Thailand Because her
movimos de Tailandia Porque a ella la
They put her in jail for her own little hotel, that person that I have cared for for more than 20 years, eh, maintained in some way and have never left alone, not aside, not apart, not in [ __ ], that person that I managed to get out of jail wants to put me in jail
de la cárcel quiere meterme en la cárcel
right now, how strong,
ahora mismo qué fuerte
eh, how heavy, eh, I mean, taking away
eh qué heavy eh o sea ya lo de quitarle
the sanctuary was, like you
el santuario era
know, it was like, cloth, it was like, to
como sabes era como tela era como to
much, no, no, no, I mean, after everything
much no ya no O sea después de todo lo
that he has given you in life and everything that he
que te ha dado en la vida y todo lo que
has done for you, eh, it
ha hecho por ti eh
was like t
ya era como t
match, [ __ ]
match [__]
and wanting to put him in
y querer meterlo en la
jail, what level, no, how
cárcel qué nivel no
heavy,
qué heavy
very crazy, very
muy loco muy
crazy, very crazy, the truth is, I hope it turns out
loco muy loco la verdad espero que salga
well, I hope it turns out
bien Espero que salga
well, we have a couple of things still, no
bien tenemos un par de cosas todavía no
places, audios of the cat are leaked. What,
lugares se filtran audios de gata What
audios of the cat are leaked about the
se filtran audios de gata sobre las
controversies of Rebor and the alleged
polémicas de rebor y la supuesta
participation of Gemita in the harassment of
participación de gemita en el acoso del
Auron's brother in his house, what, what, what, what, how
hermano de auron en su casa qué qué qué
But how is
qué cómo Pero cómo es
this, t, of the supposed new reality, let's
esto t de la supuesta nueva realidad a
see,
ver
Fortunately, they didn't realize that it
Afortunadamente no se dieron cuenta que
was me who leaked the information, I'm taking a
fui yo quien filtró la información me
big risk but  I honestly
arriesgo mucho pero Honestamente
wish he would also stay away from my
quisiera que también se alejara de mi
friend And by the way help rebor as
amigo Y de paso ayudar a rebor cómo le
you know her I know that she is
conocen ustedes sé que ella está
aware of these accounts I had my
pendiente de estas cuentas tenía mis
suspicions and she confirmed it when she uploaded
sospechas y me lo confirmó cuando subió
those videos almost minutes after
esos vídeos casi a los minutos de que
you published So I will say something that
ustedes publicaron Así que diré algo que
she will not be able to deny and she will not be able to
ella no podrá desmentir y no se podrá
invent something quickly to disassociate themselves they
inventar algo rápido para desvincularse
are taking couples therapy after
están tomando terapia de pareja luego de
rebor got upset because of things that
que rebor se pusiera mal por cosas que
he discovered and she told him that she was
él descubrió y ella le dijo que lo
leaving him it has been almost a month and obviously gata
dejaba llevan casi un mes y obvio gata
has used this to take total control
ha usado esto para tomar control total
of his public and private life She
de la vida pública y Privada de él Ella
only limits herself to saying that rebor is the
solo se limita a decir que rebor es el
problem because her community goes beyond
problema porque su comunidad va más allá
everything In addition to the fact that they consider that
de todo Además de que consideran que la
rebor's followers hate her for hating and
seguidora de rebor la odian por odiar y
that
que
she does nothing
ella no hace nada
that she is too authentic for
que es demasiado auténtica para los
others that this bothers the people
demás que eso molesta la gente a su
around her on the subject of auron and the
alrededor sobre el tema de auron y La
fight was something more than egos auron
pelea fue algo más que egos auron lo
saw him as a rival he minimized himself in front
veía como rival él se minimizaba frente
of rebor the Boom that rebor hit
a rebor el Boom que rebor pegó de la
overnight the support And
noche a la mañana el apoyo Y la
admiration of several
admiración de varios compañeros de
platform companions jealousy and bad  understood because
plataforma celos y malos entendidos por
of third parties the fight went too
culpa de terceros la pelea llegó muy
far because rebor did not fold the hand and
lejos porque rebor no dobló las mano y
in that between rebor also made a mistake she
en ese inter rebor también se equivocó
got in the middle of something that did not
se metió en medio de algo que no le
correspond to her and the fight got
correspondía y la pelea se hizo más
bigger I think that's it [ __ ] It's that they have
grande yo creo que eso a ver [__] Es
always denied it to me they have
que a mí siempre me lo han
always denied it to me the
negado a mí siempre me lo han negado lo
dimant according to the cat is motivated because
dimant según la gata es motivado porque
she rejected him
ella lo rechazó el año
last year also here Ruben had a lot to do with it he
pasado además aquí Rubén tuvo mucho que
tells them I told them Last time that
ver les dice les dije La vez pasada que
many people are going to fall from their
mucha gente se les va a caer de sus
pedestals people do many things
pedestales la gente hace muchas cosas
to reach the top and the bad thing is that it is
por llegar a la cima y lo malo es que es
momentary gata leaks information so
momentánea gata filtra información para
that people talk about her according to her she has
que se hable de ella según ella tiene
plans for a YouTube channel of her
planes para un canal de YouTube de ella
and rebor from what I understand She is
y de rebor por lo que entendí Está
trying to convince him that that would leave
tratando de convencerlo que eso dejaría
more money than spending 5 hours
más dinero que estar 5 horas
playing she leaks information to him about
jugando ella le filtra información sobre
what they say about him and how his friends
lo que dicen de él y cómo sus amigos se
make fun of his situation rebor has
burlan de su situación a rebor le da
anxiety and panic attacks
ataques de ansiedad y pánico
constantly and she doesn't care at
constantemente y a ella no le importa en
all gata and rebor are the uncomfortable neighbors
absoluto gata y rebor son los vecinos
she can't stand rebor's family  not even
a ella no no la soporta la familia de
her friends Even in the
rebor ni sus amigos Incluso en el
building there are those awkward neighbors
edificio son esos vecinos
no cat audio about the controversy with
no audio de gata sobre la polémica con
auron and rebor's brother no
auron y el hermano de rebor no el
auron's brother audio spread by such
hermano de auron audio difundido por tal
and such on
Y tal en
Twitter are viral The thing is that there is
Twitter son virales
a mess here that you do not see
Es que aquí hay un meollo que no veas
and I know that bit lunatic Ah marusela is not
e Yo sé que bit lunática Ah marusela no
called B lunatic in how mod
se llama B lunática en como mod me
wrote to me yesterday I did not know it was her bu I
escribió ayer no sabía que era ella bu
am getting confused you are crazy buf what a mess
me estoy liando que flipas buf qué lío
what a mess
qué lío
okay buah well then I do not understand anything
vale buah pues entonces no entiendo nada
because I know that she wrote to
porque yo sé que ella le escribía por
rep on discord and and like she put a lot of
discord a rep y y como que ponía muchas
things about you to try eh to get her to
cosas sobre ti para intentar eh que que
leave me And I got really pissed off at that
me dejara Y yo me cabré mucho en ese
moment I got really pissed off with Lina and such And
momento me cabré mucho con Lina y tal Y
then everything started to come out and no I did not
entonces empezó a salir todo y no no
understand anything now I am starting to understand
entendía nada ahora empiezo a entender
things please if you can no no tell her and
cosas porfa si puedes no no decírselo y
such better because I do not want now for there to be
tal mejor porque no quiero ahora que
another focus or a fight between
haya otro foco ni haya pelea entre
your community but [ __ ] yes
vuestra comunidad pero [__] sí
yes the god is bigger than I
que sí que el dio es más grande de lo
thought But well I think that has to be
que pensaba Pero bueno eso yo creo que
put aside  it doesn't matter We've
se tiene que dejar a un lado da igual Ya
stopped giving it any attention if it was that
dejamos de darlo bola si ha sido esa
girl who was messing everything up Well
chica que la ha estado liando todo Pues
look because
mira porque de verdad
I was really angry about everything that was
yo me daba mucha rabia todo lo que
happening because all the time it was
estaba pasando porque todo el rato eran
things about you that were reaching her on the network
cosas sobre ti lo que le llegaban a red
from Lina and what was reaching
por parte de Lina y lo que me llegaba a
me and I was going crazy I mean
mí y yo me Estaba volviendo loca digo
[ __ ] what's her problem weak has
[__] que qué problema tiene debil
with me that I only told her that a long time ago you
conmigo que solo le dije eso hace tiempo
know
sabes
about the whole thing regarding Gate things in the
de toda la movida referente a Gate cosas
fandom where they go crazy because of
del fandom donde se vuelven loco porque
anything We have to lower the
cualquier cosa Hay que bajarle la
intensity I don't know exactly what's going on
intensidad No sé exactamente qué pasa
with the
con el
fandom the cat thing that has rivalry
fandom el tema gata que tiene rivalidad
for whatever reason these issues have already been
por lo que sea estos temas ya están
resolved Who is Marusela yes the
solventado Quién es marusela sí la
network moderator Marusela Marusela is
moderadora de red marusela marusela es
Lina
Lina
[ __ ] but it's very complex they are
hostias pero es muy complejo están
being very harsh
siendo muy duros
Debi has been enduring harassment because
Debi ha estado aguantando acoso porque
behind her back they have been
por detrás se ha estado
lying to each other the funa of 2f they talk about this
mintiendo la funa del 2f hablan de esto
as if it were a terrorist act eh And
como si fuera un acto terrorista eh Y de
again I apologize for having exposed it
nuevo me disculpo por haberlo expuesto
live but
en directo pero es que se estaba yendo
everything was getting out of hand and
todo de madre e
because when you upload Something about me you don't eh
porque a la que subes Algo de mí tú no
in  general that goes to the
eh en general eso va a los canales de
gossip channels and ends up everywhere and the
salseo y termina en todos lados y lo
last thing I wanted is to stir up more
último que quería es remover más la
[ __ ] but oh well
[__] pero bueno
eh Tan yen and Juan haven't stopped So what does it matter what I
eh Tan yen y Juan no han parado Así que
said I can upload
qu más da lo que dijera puedo subir
screenshots and there's more [ __ ] and lots of
capturas y y hay más [__] y mucha
[ __ ] and all I want is for the
[__] y yo lo único que quiero es que
whole truth to come out because this is
salga toda la verdad porque es que esto
really horrible I mean
está siendo horrible de verdad deb O sea
if you knew the whole truth you would freak out and that's why
si supierais toda la verdad flipar y por
despite all our
eso a pesar de de todas nuestras
differences and such you could have turned your
diferencias y tal podrías haberle dado
back on rep and you're not doing it
la espalda a rep y no lo estás haciendo
and that's why I really appreciate it and I
y por eso pues te lo agradezco mucho y
hope everything comes to light soon
espero que todo salga a la luz pronto
because this is all a maneuver by a
porque todo esto es maniobra de una
person who is behind all this
persona que está detrás de todo esto
messing things up because the
liándola porque el clip de
magnetized magnetized clip doesn't know the truth and I
imantado imantado no sabe la verdad y yo
honestly don't know what else to do
sinceramente ya no sé qué más hacer
because I know everything but I'm not saying anything
porque lo sé todo pero no digo nada
because it's embarrassing to expose the truth
porque da pena exponer la verdad
for the other person and it really
por por el otro y es una verdadera
sucks because he always gets away with
[__] porque él siempre se va de
it while his mother throws [ __ ] at him
rositas mientras su madre le tira [__]
now luckily he gets along with his
ahora por suerte ya se lleva bien con el
brother and some
hermano y ya se han aclarado algunas
things have been clarified but he's very strong He
cosas pero es que es muy fuerte Es que
's very strong aunt  that Gemita took the photos from the
es muy fuerte tía que las fotos del
mailbox, you know, I'm just saying that's it, it's
buzón las saco gemita sabes solo digo
non-stop,
eso es que es no parar
Gemita took the photo of the mailbox, this is Cat fighting with the
gemita esto es gata peleándose con la
Rebor community. Ah, a lot of text, this, you bastard, a lot of
rebor Ah mucho texto esto cabrón mucho
text, this, you
texto esto
bastard, a lot, a lot of text, this, eh,
cabrón muchísimo muchísimo texto esto eh
so she's fighting with the
o sea que se pelea con la comunidad de
Rebor community, okay, well, the
rebor vale bueno es que la comunidad de
Rebor community can't really see her,
rebor en realidad no la puede ver
okay. This is about Mariana and
no vale Esto es lo de Mariana y
Valentina, that we're going to see now, but it's a
Valentina que lo vamos a ver ahora pero
real pain, the Cat doesn't start
tela marinera no la gata no se pone a
filtering, I mean, these are things that
filtrar o sea estas son cosas que filtra
she filters, eh, I mean, These are things that she leaks, she leaks
ella eh o sea Estos son cosas que ella
so that it reaches channels like
para para que llegue a los canales como
mine, eh, I mean, so much that they put on, no, no,
el mío eh o sea tanto que se ponen no no
no, the [ __ ] shitty gossip channels,
no los [__] canales de [__] de salseo
but they leak things, eh, I already knew that
pero filtran cosas eh yo ya sabía que
she talked to accounts, of course, it's known, it's known, it's known, it's known,
ella hablaba con con cuentas claro se
LoL. But hey, in reality, then Rebor
LoL Pero oye en realidad entonces rebor
speaks badly of Auron in private, I mean, she
en privado habla mal de auron o sea se
gets along well now with her brother, she has
lleva bien ahora con el hermano ha
achieved cordiality with her
conseguido una cordialidad con el
brother,
hermano
but of course with Auro, she has something deep down in her
pero claro con Auro tiene algo dentro en
chest that she hasn't told and she considers that she
el pecho que no ha contado y considera
leaves  auro
que deja a Auro
bad and he's [ __ ] because
mal y está [__] porque la madre de
auron's mother really messes with rebor But he
auron sí que se mete con rebor Pero él
has to shut up because if not everything
se tiene que callar porque si no todo
is already LoL come on this I'm telling you
está ya LoL vamos esto también te digo
this is the version of gata will be or
esto es la la versión de gata será o
will be will be or will be will be
seró será o
or will be let's
sero será o
talk about Valentina dude I'm going to
sero vamos a hablar lo de Valentina tío
put it here because
lo voy a lo voy a meter aquí porque
we were watching it on the
estuvimos viéndolo en en el canal
main channel and I don't have time to record more
principal y no me da tiempo a grabar más
videos for the main channel today I'm going to
vídeos para el canal principal hoy voy a
record about michelo you will have it in
grabar sobre michelo lo tendréis dentro
a few hours Okay but I can't record
de unas horas Vale pero no puedo grabar
seven videos a day for the
siete vídeos al día para el canal
main channel okay I don't have time for everything I don't have
principal vale no me da tiempo a todo no
time for everything yes it's true I'm
me da tiempo a todo sí que es verdad que
going to put it now I
voy a poner ahora lo pongo ahora lo
put it now I'm going to put a tweet about
pongo lo voy a poner un tweet sobre lo
gata
de gata
okay [ __ ] bomb
vale hostias bomba
ah
ah
How did he
Cómo ha dicho
literally say here photos of the mailbox the AC
literalmente aquí fotos del buzón las AC
gemita you know I'm just saying that it's that it's a
gemita sabes solo digo eso es que es un
stop LoL like the like that is
parar LoL como la como eso sea
true hosa is that if that Yes that's
verdad hosa es que si eso Si eso es
true auron doesn't like gemita
verdad a auron no le cae muy bien gemita
no Uy auron doesn't like rebor very much
no Uy a auron no le cae muy bien rebor
actually
en realidad
no  Of
no
course what's up balu you're very late Well yes well yes
Claro qué tal balu llegas muy tarde Pues
you're very late I'm only
sí pues sí llegas muy tarde Yo solamente
going to comment on one more topic I'm only going
voy a comentar un tema más Solamente voy
to comment on one more topic to leave it here
a comentar un tema más para dejarlo aquí
since noid to comment on it in the
ya que noid comentarlo en el canal
main channel but wait I put this post
principal pero es espera pongo este post
and I tell you that it is an
y os comento que es una
update of the case okay
actualización de del caso vale Ya se
Valentina has already woken up a lot of
despertó Valentina que me me reñía mucha
people scolded me the other day because I
gente el otro día porque la
called her Valentín several times but it was
llamé Valentín varias veces pero fue
luar
culpa de luar
luar's fault I always ask them with the
luar yo siempre les pregunto con los
names no Hey How do you pronounce this
nombres no Oye Cómo se pronuncia este
name I don't ask in the
nombre no lo pregunto en el grupo de
Editors group no and they usually guide me a
Editores no y ellos me suelen guiar un
little bit so I don't look so
poquito para yo no quedar tan en
ridiculous and on this occasion places I don't know
ridículo y en esta ocasión lugares no sé
where I had heard that they called him
dónde había escuchado que le llamaban
Valentín I also uh to be
Valentín Yo también eh en honor a la
honest I also heard Valentín in
verdad yo también escuché Valentín en
some video I don't remember where or from
algún vídeo no me acuerdo dónde ni de
whom okay But anyway the important thing is not
quién vale Pero bueno lo importante no
how the name is pronounced The
es como se pronuncia el nombre Lo
important thing is that she has woken up from the
importante es que se ha despertado del
induced coma she
coma inducido
woke up with anxiety due to the trauma
em despertó con ansiedad por el trauma
her mother specified that the young woman be
su madre precisó que la joven esté
accompanied by her family and will be
acompañada por su familia y pertenecerá
in intensive care So hey good
en terapia intensiva Así que Oye buena
sign it's been how many days and
señal que han pasado cuantos de días y
this can  be definitive that she will
esto puede ser definitivo de que vaya a
survive also more
sobrevivir también se han filtrado más
screenshots have been leaked where it seems Marian
capturas donde al parecer marián ya
was already looking for Valentina to
estaba buscando a valentina para
attack her meaning it was very premeditated not
atacarla o sea fue muy premeditado no
someone who was in Polanco yesterday or
alguien que ayer estuviera en Polanco o
in the park around such and such
en el parque tal alrededor de tal
send me a
mándenme
message for a photo of the baby for
mensaje por una foto de la bebé para
that I was there with my family what do you
eso yo estuve ahí con mi familia qué
need Hello Hey by pure chance
necesitas Hola Oye por pura casualidad
yesterday in Polanco Did you see this child with
ayer en Polanco No viste a este niño con
this stroller with a baby dressed like this
esta carriola con una bebé vestida así
without the hat
sin el gorrito
Oh the hospital bill is in the
Oh la cuenta del hospital va por
millions of pesos 150,000 and it is expected to
millones de pesos 150,000 y se espera
increase to much more 150,000 turkeys
que aumente a mucho más 150.000 pavos
the girl is taking to the hospital Okay
lleva la chavala a ingresar Vale faltan
all the reconstruction surgeries on her
todas las operaciones de reconstrucción
hand chest and face are missing so
de la mano el pecho y la cara por lo que
the price could
el precio podría
multiply Valentina's hospital bill
multiplicarse la cuenta hospitalaria de
could be Mariam's responsibility
Valentina podría ser responsabilidad de
man it could be it might not let's hope
mariam hombre podría podría no esperemos
not that it is
no que lo sea
not let's hope not that it is not
no esperemos no que lo sea no cuenta del
Valentin gilabert's hospital bill is already
hospital de Valentin gilabert ya es
unaffordable let me
impagable
explain legally fortunately
te explico legalmente afortunadamente
Valentina gaver is recovering
Valentina gaver se recupera
gradually but now the question is
paulatinamente pero ahora la pregunta es
Who is going to bear the expenses that
quién va a correr con los gastos que ya
apparently already amount to almost 3 million
al parecer ascienden a casi 3 millones
euros? According to the law for adolescents,
dees Según la ley para adolescentes el
payment for damages, such as
pago de la reparación del daño como es
hospital fees, can only come
el pago del hospital solo podrá venir
from the adolescent's own efforts and
del esfuerzo propio del Adolescente y no
the parents or any third party cannot be charged through criminal means, that is, they will have to
a los papás o ningún tercero es decir
do
tendrá que hacer trabaj trabajo
community service, payment in kind, or is it paid
comunitario un pago en especie o se paga
with the adolescent's assets? Do
con los bienes que tenga el adolescente
you think Mariane has this money,
Tú crees que mariane tenga este dinero
the only solution is to charge the... Let's see, the
la única solución es cobrarle a la A ver
influencer doesn't have many followers, no,
influencer no tiene muchos seguidores no
apparently not, and she worked with many
por lo visto no y trabajaba con muchas
brands and also the prices are high
marcas y además los precios son altos a
unless she has squandered a lot,
no ser que haya derrochado muchísimo
man, I don't know if she will have all the money. I do
hombre no sé si tendrá todo el dinero Yo
n't have it, but at least she
no lo tengo pero una parte por lo menos
won't have part of it anymore, not the mother, who we already know
no tendrá ya no a la mamá que ya sabemos
doesn't have a father, if she does, she has plenty of
que no tiene papá si lo tiene le sobra
civil means, whether it's an embargo, well, man,
la vía civil ya sea embargo bien hombre
what we were talking about in the
lo que estuvimos hablando en el vídeo
main channel video is that it was clear that
del Canal principal es que se veía que
this aunt had good
esta tía tenía tenía buenas
collaborations and she didn't lack
colaboraciones y no le faltaban las
visits from followers and so on, that's
visitas a los seguidores y demás es
enough, bah my mother,
suficient bah madre mía
uncle my mother Well, of course
tío madre mía Pues claro que lo debería
she should pay for it, what
pagar ella qué
balls Marian Gonzaga leaked
[__] Marian gonzaga filtró fotos
intimate photos of another influencer in revenge
íntimas de otra influencer en venganza
a few months ago what a garment eh for
hace unos meses no menuda prenda eh para
this she insisted that the photos she
esto ella insistía que las fotos que
uploaded did not show my face Of course
subió no se veía mi cara Claro que se
my face was seen she had uploaded them without my
veía mi cara las había subido sin mi
consent and how Here I am
consentimiento y como les Aquí les estoy
telling you again about the photos that
diciendo otra vez lo de las fotos que
were private and the age that those
eran privadas y la edad que tenían esos
tial Stay until the end to
tial Quédate hasta el final para
understand how this could have been prevented
entender cómo se pudo haber prevenido
the girl we heard is
esto la chica que escuchamos es una
another victim of Mariann
víctima más de mariann a ella se le
her intimate images were leaked being
filtraron sus imágenes íntimas siendo
a minor therefore
una menor de edad por lo tanto le aplica
the trafficking law applies to her Here are the crimes
la ley de trata Aquí están los delitos
that deserve a custodial sentence
que merecen sanción privativa de
and she could get
libertad y ella pudiera lograr que se le
Mari to get C more years Well the
den C años más a Mari Pues en la ley de
trafficking law contemplates not for being a child
trata se contempla la no por infantil
Mariana I have committed countless crimes
Mariana he cometido un sinfín de delitos
here she smashed a bottle into another
aquí le estrelló una botella a otra eso
we saw that in the main that I could not
lo vimos en el principal que no pude
put the video obviously because
poner el vídeo evidentemente porque
YouTube does not allow it or like the time she
YouTube no te lo permite o como la vez
falsely accused her ex-partner or
que acusó falsamente a su expareja o
from the moment she narrates that she
desde el momento que ella narra que la
goes if she is crazy eh or  be it's zbad
vaya si está zumbada eh o sea está zbad
ima eh I mean but this is already a person
ima eh o sea pero esto ya es una persona
who is crazy zbad eh they expelled from
que está zumbadas zbad eh expulsaron de
school but none of the other
la escuela pero ninguno de los otros
teenagers reported being able to have
adolescentes denunciaron pudiendo haber
requested family supervision
solicitado una supervisión familiar
because It is evident that something in their
porque Es evidente que algo en su
environment was happening do you really think
entorno estaba pasando de verdad crees
that increasing the penalties is the solution
que aumentar las penas sea la solución
without early supervision of these
sin una supervisión temprana de estas
families mother of
familias madre de
God opinion of Jos
Dios opinión de Jos
stop everything that is happening with the
stop todo lo que está pasando con los
influencers that at some point well you
influencers que en alguna vez pues tú te
saw my with the law yes And that now well it
viste mis con la ley sí Y que ahora pues
is highlighting the
está resaltando los titulares de las
news headlines with the fojo Márquez with this
noticias con el fojo Márquez con esta
girl
chica
that oh how strong isn't it very strong
que ay qué fuerte no está muy fuerte
everything that is happening eh I think that it is
todo lo que está pasando eh yo creo que
not just the influencers I think that it
no es nada más los influencers creo que
is a reflection of our society because it
es un reflejo de nuestra sociedad porque
also happens every day all the
también pasa todos los días todo el
time with different people Of course we
tiempo con diferentes personas Claro que
put more focus on them because that is what
a ellos les ponemos más el foco porque
becomes media because they are well
es lo que se hace mediático porque son
known But I think that it is time to
conocidos Pero creo que es momento de
just see that they are going to leave
justo ir viendo que ellos van a salir
sooner or later two three 5 17 years old they are going
tarde o temprano dos tres 5 17 años van
to return to our society and
a regresar a nuestra sociedad y
we need to ask ourselves How are they going to
necesitamos preguntarnos Cómo van a
return no and what are we doing to
regresar no y qué estamos haciendo para
stop  reinsert slabs in an
para reinsertar losos de una forma
optimal way your book How it goes
óptima tu libro Cómo
there it goes there it goes est I'm working on
va ahí va ahí va est estoy trabajando en
the end but oh It's that I lack
el final pero ay Es que me falta
time networks and what is your message now
tiempo redes y cuál es tu mensaje ahora
if you are going to return to the
si es que vas a regresar a las
networks I am still on the networks there you
redes Yo sigo en las redes ahí estoy me
can look for me on tikt on Instagram on
pueden buscar en tikt en Instagram en
Facebook what I don't have is YouTube I don't
Facebook lo que no tengo es YouTube no
know if YouTube will ever let me
sé si YouTube algún día me va a dejar
have a channel we are not waiting but oh
tener un canal no estamos esperando pero
well You can follow me, the
bueno Me pueden seguir lo de
YouTube thing, the YouTube thing was a topic of a lot of
YouTube lo de YouTube fue tema muy
political pressure, a lot of media pressure,
presión política muy presión mediática
no I mean Anyway, I think I
no O sea De todas maneras ya creo que sí
could also no I mean there are a lot of
podría también no o sea es que hay mucha
people who have done
gente que ha hecho barbaridades
worse atrocities, a lot of people who and do them, you
peores mucha gente que que y las hace
know, but well I understand that it was
sabes pero bueno entiendo que era la
here politics got involved and a
aquí se metió la política de por medio y
lot got involved, a lot of things got
se metió much se metieron muchas cosas
involved eh I haven't seen the Fatima thing
de por medio eh lo de Fátima no lo he
but I'm going to bring a guest, I'll
visto pero voy a traer a una invitada ya
tell you who to the main Channel,
os diré quién al Canal principal
probably tomorrow or the day after Okay and I'll have
seguramente mañana o pasado Vale y
a talk about all these topics
tendré una charla de todos los temas
in Mexico with her in a live show, I mean you'll
estos de México con ella en un directo o
probably have it I don't know if
sea lo tendréis seguramente No sé si
tomorrow the day after or something like that But oh
mañana pasado o algo por el estilo Pero
well Likewise, heen
bueno Igualmente heen Wolf exactamente
Wolf exactly good example heen Wolf good example but I understand that I understand that J stop you can now open a channel you can now open I mean if I'm not mistaken when they close your YouTube channels or something happens to you with YouTube the thing expires in a few years it's been
YouTube la cosa caduca en unos años ya
more than five
han pasado más de cinco
for sure on the networks I share like my
segurísimo en las redes comparto como mi
day
d día cosas de
maternity things nothing more no no
maternidad nada más no ya nada de
clinics or anything by Elo for Valentina
clínicas ni nada por Elo para Valentina
who is still in the hospital bed it is
que sigue en la cama del hospital se
commented they are removing the sedation
Comenta le están quitando la sedación
little by little word
poco a poco palab
for her family Because it must be very
para su familia Porque debe ser muy
difficult because of what they are going through and I hope she
difícil por lo que están pasando y ojalá
recovers soon because I know that she
se recupere pronto porque sé que apenas
is barely like coming out of the worst
está como saliendo de lo de lo peor
And well a lot of therapy too because what she
Y pues mucha terapia también porque lo
went through was very traumatic And yes she must
que vivió fue muy traumático Y sí debe
be very well known no you hadn't heard
estar muy conocas no no habías escuchado
of her No the truth is no she is very
hablar de ella No la verdad no está muy
young do you think that suddenly the law is
chiquita crees que de pronto la ley se
harsher on
ensaña más con los
influencers and that suddenly because of The
influencers y que de repente por por El
example public figures and that they have been
ejemplo figuras públicas y que han sido
harsher with people who are
más duros con las personas que son
figures yes without a doubt I think it works
figuras sí sin duda yo creo que te juega
against you it is like exemplary  they have done
en contra es como ejemplar lo han hecho
totally and And well yes yes yes the law
totalmente y Y pues sí sí sí la ley
plays a role, it weighs heavily when you are a
juega o sea pesa mucho cuando tú eres
public figure and we'll see what happened with
figura pública y es veremos a ver lo de
Mr. Doctor, eh, I mean, Mister Doctor, it's
Mr doctor eh o sea lo de Mister doctor
not a joke eh
poca broma eh
but I think that is going to be a
pero yo creo que esa va a ser una
sentence that is also going to be important
condena que también va a ser importante
eh I mean, the guy is taking a bath in the
eh o sea está el tío pegándose el baño
masses believing that it's going well, no,
de de masas creyendo que bueno va no que
how good, no because I'm gaining many
qué bueno no porque estoy ganando muchas
visits and many followers and I'm
visitas y muchos seguidores y estoy
feeling no, that people adore me and
sintiendo no que la gente me adora y me
follow me and support me, I know in campaigns, for
sigue y me apoya ya se en campañas para
me no But what with Mr. Doctor could be
mí no Pero lo de Mr doctor puede ser una
something that ends up that what the [ __ ] that then
cosa que acabe que que [__] que luego lo
once that once you're inside
una vez que una vez que estás dentro de
the prison people are going to forget about
la prisión la gente se va a olvidar de
you You know once you're inside the
ti Sabes una vez que estés dentro de la
prison people leave they're not going to be
prisión la gente se va no van a estar
at the prison doors every day
todos los días en la puerta de la cárcel
Oh well my doctors We love you well
Ay bien mis doctor Te queremos bueno en
anyway family 2750 super chat the truth is that
fin familia 2750 super chat la verdad es
I am always very happy with the
que estoy muy contento siempre con el
support that you give us eh and I love you
apoyo que nos dais eh y os quiero
very much The truth is that you are the best
muchísimo La verdad que sois la mejor
community on the internet both the
comunidad de internet tanto la
gentlemen,
señoreros
em we have a video on the channel
em tenemos un vídeo en el canal
main thing that I uploaded today has
principal que he subido hoy me ha
really pissed me off I would appreciate it if you all
pinchado bastante os agradecería a todos
stopped by there, said the like,
que os pasáis por ahí dirais el like
commented and stuff like that, it's not about
comentaris y esas cosas no eres sobre
Joaquín Campo and the fight he's
Joaquín Campo y la pelea que está
having with Juan Goina and now I'm going to
teniendo con Juan goina y ahora voy a
record as soon as I let you I'm going to record the
grabar en cuant os deje voy a grabar el
video that you'll have inside in
videíto que tendréis dentro de dentro de
a few hours so okay I'm going now so I do
unas horillas así que bueno me voy ya
n't get into any more trouble I'm sending you all a
para no liarme más os mando un beso
huge kiss and tomorrow at least
enorme y mañana por lo menos corrillos
we have groups okay at least video on the
tenemos vale por lo menos vídeo en el
main channel there's one or two there's one or
canal principal hay uno o dos hay uno o
two at least there's a group between
dos por lo menos Corrillo hay entre
gossip Okay and I'll see if there's a live show on
salseos Vale y Ya veré si hay directo en
the main channel with this woman who I'll
el principal con esta mujer que ya os
tell you who she is and I'm sending you all a huge kiss
diré quién es y os mando un beso enorme
you're the best thank you very much good
sois los mejores muchas gracias buenas
night and I hope you had a great time
noches y espero que lo hayáis pasado muy
very good A kiss handsome
bien muy bien Un beso guapos
[Music]
[Música]